we've done deep dive research studies on
我们进行了深入的研究，探讨
how can we help everyone to become more
如何帮助每个人在约会中取得更大的
successful daters so what makes data
成功。那么，是什么让数据变得
successful So the faster that you can
成功呢？你越快
the faster you're going to find someone
找到合适的人，就能越快找到那个“
who's like yes this is the type of
没错，这就是
person that I want to be
我想在一起的那种人”。
with Justin McLoud the founder and CEO
贾斯汀·麦克劳德是
of the fastest growing dating app hinge
增长最快的约会应用Hinge的创始人兼首席执行官。他说：“
I built hinge because I wanted a
我创建Hinge是因为我想要一个
girlfriend but we had to suffer through
女朋友，但我们经历了
a lot of failure to finally get to
很多失败才最终获得
success why does the world need another
成功。” 为什么世界还需要另一个
dating app I think it just needs one
约会应用呢？我认为只需要一个
really that works well I'm going to be
真正好用的约会应用就够了。说实话，我以前从
I never used dating apps is I had no
不用约会应用的主要原因就是我没
success so if I wanted to be the world's
成功过。所以，如果我想成为世界上
worst dating app user what would I have
最糟糕的约会应用用户，我该怎么
to do a lot of filtered photos with you
做呢？和你一起拍很多滤镜照片，戴着
and sunglasses are hanging out with a
墨镜，和
lot of friends one-word answers to your
很多朋友出去玩，像其他人一样，对你的问题只回答一个词。还有，
about serial datas some of us have
我们有些人
models in our head that are exceedingly
脑子里有一些非常
narrow they have to be over 6ot and need
狭隘的模型，这些模型必须超过6000个，并且需要符合
to work in this type of job and so you
某种类型的工作要求。所以你
go out and you're just looking for some
出去约会，只是为了找个
reason to say no because it doesn't fit
理由拒绝，因为对方不符合
your model give people more of a chance
你的标准。 人工智能模型能给人们更多机会。
AI the conversation around Ai and
关于人工智能和
relationships has always been quite
人际关系的讨论一直相当
pessimistic sex robots and stuff yeah
悲观，比如性爱机器人之类的。当然，
that's certainly not going to be what a
这肯定不是
Hing is working
Hing正在努力的方向。
on the bigger leap though is to move
更大的飞跃是朝着
much closer to a Matchmaker model and
更接近“媒人”模式的方向发展，
setting up dates with a much higher
安排约会的
likelihood of success it's happening
成功率更高。这种情况已经出现了。以前需要
swipes in order to get on a date and now
滑动上千次才能约到会，现在只需要
about 50 likes have you seen any changes
大约50个赞。你觉得
in the dating culture yeah in order to
约会文化有什么变化吗？是的，为了
get on a date people need to know this
约到会，人们需要知道这一点。还有一个问题，
quick one this is really really
这让
fascinating to me on the back end of our
我非常感兴趣。在我们的
YouTube channel it says that
YouTube频道后台，数据显示，在我们
channel haven't yet hit the Subscribe
频道运营期间，经常观看我们频道的观众中有69.9%还没有点击“订阅”
button I just wanted to ask you a favor
按钮。我只是想请你们帮个忙。
it helps this channel so much if you
如果您选择订阅，这对我们频道的帮助非常大，可以
the guest helps us scale the production
帮助我们扩大嘉宾阵容，扩大节目制作规模，让
and it makes this show bigger so if I
节目更受欢迎。所以，如果
could ask you for one favor if you've
您
watched the show before and you've
之前看过我们的节目，并且
enjoyed it and you like this episode
喜欢它，也喜欢
that you're currently watching could you
您正在观看的这一集，请您
please hit the Subscribe button thank
点击“订阅”按钮。
you so much and I will repay that
非常感谢，我会尽我所能，
gesture by making sure that everything
确保我们在
we do here gets better and better and
这里所做的一切都越来越好，
better and better that is a promise I'm
这是我的承诺。
deal Justin what is your job title I'm
贾斯汀，我们有音乐方面的合作吗？你的职位是什么？我是
the founder and CEO of hinge and to
Hinge的创始人兼CEO。为了
quantify what hinge is and the impact it
量化Hinge是什么，以及它对
has on the world how many people use as
世界的影响，比如有多少人使用它，
a product its reach can you give me some
它的覆盖范围有多
color towards that uh well I I can say
广，你能具体说说吗？嗯，我可以告诉你，
that today we're setting up a date about
现在我们平均每
every two seconds so every other second
两秒钟就促成一次约会，也就是说，每隔一秒钟就
someone's going on a date because of
有人因为
hinge um we've created millions of
Hinge而约会。我们已经促成了数百万段
relationships and I'd say marriages at
关系，我
think what I imagined when I when I
想说，现在的规模远远超出了我当初
started this thing I probably need to
创办Hinge时的设想。我可能需要更深入地
understand you a little bit better
了解你，
because it's so abundantly clear from
因为我
all the CEOs that I've interviewed that
采访过的所有CEO都清楚地表明，他们
that there's often a series of catalyst
往往经历了一系列的催化剂
moments that send them on the path
时刻，间接地推动他们走上了这条道路。
indirectly I mean it's like the first
我的意思是，就像
Domino that falls in their life that
他们生命中倒下的第一张多米诺骨牌，让
brings them to be sat here today for us
他们今天坐在这里和我们
to be talking about it what are those
谈话。
first dominoes in your life that film I
电影里提到的那些在你人生中最初的几张多米诺骨牌是什么？
I don't think there are a number of them
我觉得并没有很多，但它们
that probably like ended up defining my
最终定义了我
my life I was an only child um had a
的人生。我是独生子，我父亲是个
entrepreneur father who had ran a small
企业家，经营着一家小
business and um and my mom worked for my
公司，我母亲也为我父亲工作。我从小就
math I was good at computer science uh I
数学很好，也擅长计算机科学，我夏天会去
would spend my summers at nerd Camp uh
书呆子夏令营学习编程。
kid and I will say addiction is the last
我会说，成瘾是最后一个
piece because I I wanted I like was
因素，因为我渴望，我迫切地想要
desperate to be cool as desperate to fit
变得很酷，渴望融入群体，
in and that actually became like a huge
而这实际上也成了
piece of it as well for me in your first
我人生中非常重要的一部分。
year of University you went to see a
你大学一年级的时候去看过
drug and alcohol counselor is that
戒毒戒酒咨询师，对吗？是的。
correct I did so when I went to college
我上大学的时候，
you know it was I would say the
可以说我身上那种追求
overachieving part of me started to slip
卓越的特质开始消失，我反而更加沉迷于喝酒、
the uh drinking and drugs and partying
吸毒和派对。大一结束的时候，
freshman year I thought to myself like
我心想，
gosh you know like I haven't been to bed
天哪，自从开学以来，我从来没有
sober since school began like not one
清醒地睡过觉。 就一个
single night and maybe I have a problem
晚上，我可能真的有问题，
like maybe something's going on here so
可能有什么事要发生了，所以
I I voluntarily went in to see this drug
我主动去找了一位戒毒
an alcohol counselor it's like very
戒酒咨询师，她
sweet woman named
叫
Jane and she listened to me
简，人特别好。她很理解我，也很
empathetically and heard me out and she
认真地听我倾诉。她说：“
was like Justin you know I I think that
贾斯汀，我觉得
you probably have a pretty serious
你可能真的有很严重的
problem with drugs and alcohol I think
毒品和酒精问题，
that you should definitely keep coming
你应该经常来找
back and seeing me and I think you
我，你
should stop and I was like whoa whoa
应该戒掉。” 我当时就懵了，心想：哇哇哇哇，
what are you talking about I'm like a
你在说什么？我才
19-year-old kid so I just kind of
19岁啊！所以我就
ignored that and went about the the
没理会她的话，继续我的派对生活。
partying um but I had some inkling at
不过那时候我确实隐隐觉得情况不太妙。
good you went to rehab eventually I did
你最终还是去了戒毒所。我的确去了，
my freshman year in order to even come
大一结束后，我不得不去戒毒所待了一个暑假，才能
back to school because I I would I'd
继续上学。因为我经常
still get in trouble a lot at like with
惹麻烦，比如被
campus safety or whatever getting caught
校园安全部门抓到
drinking or uh and I'd been written up
喝酒什么的，我被警告的
so many times that I actually got
次数太多了，最后不得不再次回到戒毒所。
she's like well I've already actually
我去找了戒毒戒酒咨询师做评估，她说：“我已经
assessed this kid he clearly has a
评估过这孩子了，他显然有
problem so I had to spend my summer in
问题。”所以我不得不在暑假去戒毒所待一段时间，才能顺利升入大二。
sophomore year so many people I've
我跟很多人
spoken to had an alcohol addiction at
聊过，他们都曾有过酗酒的经历，也都
some point in their life speak about the
谈到过
12 step program and the role that that
十二步疗法以及它在
played in them turning their lives
他们人生转变中所起的作用。你是什么时候
around did you when did did you learn
了解到
about the 12 step program at alen did it
艾伦学院的十二步疗法的？它对你有帮助吗？确实有
help I did and I would occasionally go
帮助。我偶尔会去参加互助小组的
to meetings and they were
会议，但参加的都是
like people from the town like no one no
镇上的人，
no one from like college was going to
没有大学生会去。
these I was literally the only college
我几乎是唯一一个戒酒的
student I did stop drinking the the and
大学生。
the day that I graduated from college
毕业那天，
and um and 12-step programs was like a
十二步疗法对
huge piece of of my recovery after that
我的康复起到了至关重要的作用。
night before was graduating that day I'd
毕业那天，我前一天晚上参加了一个派对，第二天早上醒来，发现毕业那天我
gotten a okay job in Washington DC where
在华盛顿特区找到了一份还不错的工作，准备
School
毕业后搬过去。
ended but I just remember thinking to
但我记得当时我心里想，
like that the steering wheel in my life
我的人生方向盘
was broken that's kind of how I and I
坏了。 就是这样，我
think that gets back to your sort of
觉得这又回到了你说的
enslavement idea or that you just don't
奴役感，或者说你不再能
have have control anymore like I
掌控自己的生活。我曾经
envisioned my life going like this
设想过自己的人生会朝着这个
direction like I I wanted to have a big
方向发展，我想要一份伟大的
career I wanted to go make an impact in
事业，想要对
the world I wanted to have like deep
世界产生影响，想要拥有深厚的
friendships I wanted all these things
友谊，我想要所有这些。
and yet every day it was like one more
然而，每天我都想着再喝一杯，再吸一口
drink right one more drug and tomorrow
毒，然后告诉自己明天
longer am I going to allow this to
我就要开始重整旗鼓了。我已经这样告诉自己好几年了。我记得当时我在想，如果戒酒，我不知道活着的意义是什么，但我还是要试着去寻找答案。我当时就在想，我还要让这种情况持续多久？
continue to to go like I I I didn't get
我没能得到
the job that I wanted right I wanted I
我想要的工作，我
wanted to go work at uh you know Goldman
想去高盛银行工作，那是
just like what the I was a mathematical
我大学主修数理经济学，也是
economics major and that's what all like
所有
the top math econ Majors went and
顶尖数理经济学毕业生最终的归宿，
did and and I didn't I didn't get the
而我却没有。 我没找到那份
job I got some like you know decent job
工作，后来在华盛顿特区
at some management consulting firm that
一家名不见经传的管理咨询公司找到了一份还算不错的工作。
and uh I'd lost the girl which we
呃，我失去了女朋友，我们
haven't talked about Kate yet but my I
还没聊到凯特，我
had a girlfriend all through college and
大学期间一直有女朋友，后来
I'd like lost her it's just it was just
失去了她。
my life was like not headed in a good
我的生活当时
direction it was so clear and I just
明显走错了方向，我把那看作是一个
viewed that as a moment to like change
改变的契机。
it when did you meet
你是什么时候认识
Kate I met Kate the basically like
凯特的？我基本上是在我戒毒所出来的那天认识凯特的，我晚上
like got out of rehab at 8 p.m. one
8点从戒毒所出来的。
night in Louisville Kentucky I Drove All
在肯塔基州路易斯维尔的一个晚上，我连夜开车
Night back to school and uh and I woke
回学校。
up the next day and decided to celebrate
第二天醒来后，我决定庆祝自己戒毒成功，
getting out of rehab by going out and
出去
partying and drinking and uh Kate found
玩玩喝酒。凯特发现
me passed out in a stairwell like on the
我醉倒在楼梯间，就在
landing of a stairwell uh the first day
楼梯平台那边。
of my sophomore year was her first day
我大二开学的第一天，也是她大一
of school first day of her freshman year
开学的第一天。
later in that year we had a class
那年晚些时候，我们一起上了一门课，
together we started sitting together we
开始坐在一起，
started get to know each other and we
开始互相了解。我们之间有一种
just had this incredible like magnetic
不可思议的、像磁铁一样的
connection when you reflect on meeting
联系。回想当初遇见
her and
她时的感受，以及所有的一切，
I mean you now are working in the
你现在在这个行业工作，回首往事，有没有什么感觉和当时发生的一切一致，比如，你现在通过
know all the people that hinge has
Hinge平台认识了这么多人，而这些都与你
brought together today that happened in
现在的成就相符？
that moment because you know you see on
你知道，
the movies they say you'll feel this
电影里会说，你会感到
thing in your belly and there'll be
心跳加速，
butterflies and they'll be crazy you
小鹿乱撞，激动不已等等。
your experience like did you have
你的经历是怎样的？你当时有这种感觉吗？你
butterflies did you know she they were
知道她就是你的真命天女吗？
one um I think I I'm not sure it was was
嗯……我想……我不确定。 就像
like the moment I saw Kate like I knew
我第一眼见到凯特的时候，我就知道
she was the one but I think the our our
她就是我的真命天女。但我觉得我们之间的
like relationship really started to
关系是随着
build as we got to know each other
彼此了解的加深才真正建立起来的。
better and so it wasn't for me like one
所以对我来说，这并不是那种一见钟情的感觉，而是随着
really quickly as we got to know each
我们彼此了解的加深，感情发展得非常迅速。
better whether that spark is a good
至于这种火花是好是
thing or a bad thing I think has been
坏，我觉得一直以来都有
debated I know you had Logan our our
争议。我知道你请了Logan做我们
relationship scientist on um from hinge
关系专家的节目，在Hinge上。
and I think the spark can sort of like
我觉得火花可能会慢慢
burn out and what you're looking for is
熄灭，而你真正想要的其实是那种
really like a nice SL burn within two
美好的、逐渐消退的感情。两年内
years you had broken up oh we' broken up
你们就分手了。哦，我们分分合合了
seven times I think during college and
六七次，我想是在大学期间。
then finally by the end of college we'd
最后，在大学毕业的时候，我们
really like gone our separate ways once
彻底分道扬镳了。
I gotten sober um I would think about
我戒酒之后，我总是会想重新联系
reaching back out to her all the time
她，
but I just wouldn't because I had enough
但我最终还是放弃了，因为我足够
sense to realize that like I had
理智，意识到我
probably like messed up this girl's life
可能已经把她的人生搞得
enough and um it just like wasn't
够糟的了，这样下去并不
healthy and so I would I remember being
健康。所以，我记得大概过了
like a year or two years sober and I
一两年…… 我当时很清醒，
would like you know dial her number on
你知道，我会拨通她的号码，然后盯着
it and then I would just like hit the
它看，最后按下挂断
end button and I just didn't
键。
feel I just didn't feel like I was good
我感觉自己
for her and I and I just need to stay
配不上她，我需要
away and when you ultimately end up
远离她。但最终我还是
reaching out to her when she's living in
联系了她，那时她住在
London and working in
伦敦，在
finance yeah so I I four years in I'm
金融行业工作。四年过去了，我
sober I'm at business school and I I
戒酒了，在商学院读书。
finally I'm like okay I'm going to like
最后，我想，好吧，我要给
write her a letter like an apology
她写封信，一封道歉
letter um and see if we can reconnect
信，看看我们能不能重新联系上。我给她
and I I wrote her this letter and she
写了这封信，那时她已经
was living in she' moved to London at
搬到伦敦了。
point and she called me back the next
第二天她给我回了电话，
day and she was with someone at the time
当时她和别人在一起。她说，圣诞节
and she's like well I'm going to be home
我会回家，
for Christmas time so maybe I can see
也许圣诞节我们可以见一面。
you at Christmas time and then she
然后她又
called me back the next day and she's
打来电话，说，
like listen I just if I see you I don't
听着，如果我见到你，我不
know what's going to happen happen
知道会发生什么。
just uh I have a stable life now I have
我现在生活稳定，有
a partner we just bought a flat like I
伴侣，我们…… 我买了套公寓，但我
just can't and so I was just totally
做不到，所以我当时真的
heartbroken because I really thought in
心碎了，因为我一直觉得，
the back of my mind like someday we I
总有一天我们会在一起，我
just felt like we were like meant to be
觉得我们注定要
together and I thought like one day
在一起，我觉得总有一天
we're we're going to end up back
我们会重归于好。
together and I think in that moment I
我想在那一刻我
realized like wow I've really messed
意识到，哇，我真的搞砸了，一切都无法挽回了。
back you were at Harvard at the time
你当时在哈佛，是的，
single you're sober which makes it hard
你是单身，而且戒酒了，这让你很难
to meet people I guess precisely I mean
认识新朋友，我想正是如此。我的意思是，
that's the thing is I is I um both it
问题在于，我
was very special with her and also I
和她之间非常特别，而且我真的
really had trouble meeting other other
很难认识其他
people like I really relied on drugs and
人，我非常依赖毒品和
alcohol as a crutch and when I graduated
酒精。毕业后，我全身心
I threw myself into work and then I but
投入工作，然后
then I arrived at business school where
我去了商学院，顺便说一下，
I think by the way we're there to like
我们去那里是为了
study business but it's like a huge
学习商业，但那里的氛围就像一个巨大的
party atmosphere and like everyone
派对，每个人都通过
connects around drinking and and
喝酒和
partying and I just just
聚会来建立联系，我真的
couldn't it was like just too hard for
做不到，
me to be around any of that it was hard
我很难融入那种环境，很难
for me to meet new people I mean that's
认识新朋友。 我的意思是，
the case for so many of us today so many
现在很多人都是这样，很多
people who much of the reason it feels
人之所以
like they continue to drink and do those
继续喝酒，继续做那些
things which they don't necessarily love
他们并不喜欢的事情，很大程度上
is because it's almost unavoidable if
是因为如果你想喝酒，几乎无法避免；
you want to it seems unavoidable if you
如果你
want to socialize and be not be
想社交，不想被
perceived as a weirdo yeah and just the
视为怪人，似乎也无法避免。是的，
whole culture and the whole like that it
整个文化等等，一切都
was just all revolved around drinking so
围绕着喝酒，所以人们总是
it was just constantly saying no
说“不”，
constantly saying no thanks I don't
总是说“不，谢谢，我不
drink like is this at all correlated you
喝酒”。这和
know you're in that situation where you
你
you've given up drinking you bit
戒酒后有点
heartbroken does this also explain why
心碎的情况有关系吗？这也能解释为什么
you were so compelled to do something in
你如此渴望在
the dating
约会
space there was a business plan like a
领域做些什么吗？当时有个商业计划，
business school like business plan
就像商学院的商业计划
competition and so I was working on like
比赛，我为此构思了
a few ideas for
一些想法，
that and nothing really hit like I was
但没有一个真正奏效。
trying to work on I had like various
我有一些零
little silly ideas and I try to work on
零碎碎的小想法，也尝试着去实现
them but
它们，但
it always just felt like homework and I
感觉就像在做作业，
just like wasn't getting much
没什么进展。就在
after everything had happened with Kate
凯特的事情发生后不久，
and she you know told me in so many
她告诉我…… 当时说了好多
words that like it was time to move on
话，感觉是时候该向前看了。
party happening at at Harvard where
哈佛有个“最后机会舞会”，
people were going to like list all their
大家可以在上面列出自己
crushes and then if two people like
暗恋的人，如果两个人互相
listed each other they would like let
列出了对方，舞会开始
you know right before the dance so this
前就会通知对方。这就像是“
was like a moment of like okay like
好吧，
we're heading towards the end of school
我们快要毕业了”，
I think it was around Valentine's Day
我记得好像是情人节前后。
and so this is like your last chance
所以，如果你大二的时候暗恋过谁，这就是你最后的机会了。
moment to find out I was actually like
我当时其实
pretty excited about this because like I
挺兴奋的，因为
again I was like so awkward like I
我真的很笨拙，
didn't know how to like connect with
不知道怎么跟
people or meet new people I just like I
人交流，也不知道怎么认识新朋友。我
didn't know how to do that without the
不知道不用
crutch of of alcohol and drugs and I was
酒精和毒品该怎么做到。有一天，我和
the um student body president this guy
学生会主席
Brett and he was like Yeah we actually
布雷特一起去上课，他说：“我们
decided to scrap that whole thing it was
决定取消那个活动了，
just too complicated like a thousand
太复杂了，上千
people all listing each other like how
个人互相列出来，
are we going to manage all the you know
我们怎么管理啊，太难了，所以我们
like too hard like we just scrapped that
取消了。”
whole thing I I I went to class I
我去上课，
started sitting there I started thinking
坐在教室里。 我开始思考，心想
like I bet I could just like build this
我肯定能
really quick on Facebook like I I I used
在Facebook上很快地做出这个东西。我以前写过
to code I like knew how these kind
代码，知道这些
things worked and Facebook had recently
东西是怎么运作的。而且Facebook最近
opened up their API for canvas apps like
开放了像Farmville之类的Canvas应用的API，
Farmville and things like that I was
我就想，
like you could just like go through and
你可以直接
just check your friends that you liked
查看你喜欢的朋友，然后
this really quick on Facebook so I
在Facebook上快速搭建一个类似的功能。于是我
enlisted a friend um
找了一个朋友，
her name was Francis and we got together
她叫弗朗西斯，我们一起
and we built this thing um where people
做了这个东西，让人们可以
could like list their crushes on
在Facebook上列出自己喜欢的人，
Facebook and would tell you if two
然后告诉你两个
people matched and we launched it and it
人是否匹配。我们上线了，它
made a bunch of matches it was fun and
促成了很多匹配，很有趣，
people had like a good time but then it
大家都玩得很开心。但是，
was you know you find out if you have a
你知道，当你发现自己是否喜欢某人时，要么
crush you either do or you don't and
喜欢，要么不喜欢，
then everyone's done with it but the
然后大家就都结束了。但这个
idea then started to to like percolate
想法开始
in my mind like what if you could
在我脑海里酝酿：如果能把
actually introduce people to their
人们介绍给他们
friends of friends because at the
朋友的朋友呢？因为当时虽然有在线
time there was there were online dating
约会
sites but no one my age used them
网站，但我这个年纪的人都不用，人们
there's a lot of stigma around it
对它们有很多偏见，
because it was like a long arduous
因为那是一个漫长而繁琐的
process you did on desktop computers you
过程，需要在电脑上完成。 你曾经用电脑
answered like deep questions about
回答过很多关于自己的深刻问题，
yourself you paid a lot of money usually
通常还要花很多钱
to use them and the idea of like
才能使用它们。突然，我脑海里冒出一个想法：
creating something like really simple
创造一个简单
and easy that would just connect you to
易用的东西，能让你和
friends of friends suddenly just like
朋友的朋友联系起来。
popped in my mind and I don't know how
我不知道该怎么
to describe it I just like I was so
形容那种感觉，我当时
excited about this idea I was convinced
对这个想法兴奋不已，坚信
this going to be the future of how
这将是未来
people were going to date and I like
人们约会的方式。我根本
couldn't stop working on it and to set
停不下来，一直在努力开发。
the scene though a little bit this is at
不过，为了稍微描述一下当时的场景，我得说说当时的情况。那时候已经有了
there's like Okay Cupid match.com but
Okay Cupid和Match.com，但还没有
there's not like mobile dating apps
移动约会应用，对吧？没错，当时根本没有移动约会应用，也
nothing was mobile and nothing no one
没人
really used it or if you used it you
真正使用，就算用了，也不会到处
didn't really talk about it like people
谈论。像
my age just like didn't use or talk
我这个年纪的人，根本不用也不谈论
about online dating services that was
在线约会服务，那根本不存在。“
just not a thing the term dating app was
约会应用”这个词当时甚至都
not even a term yet do you think that's
还没出现。你觉得这是为什么呢？
a because I so many people asked me the
因为很多人问我，
question about how to know which idea to
怎么才能知道该选择哪个想法。
pursue many entreprene types creatives
很多创业者和创意人士
have lots of ideas they have a Shelf
都有很多想法，他们脑子里堆满了各种点子。
full of them yeah um how do we know
嗯，该怎么做呢？ 我们知道
which one is the one worth
哪个才是值得
pursuing I I can only speak to my
追求的。我只能谈谈我自己的
experience like I don't know what the
经历，我不知道哪个才是
right what the right answer is but I
真正的正确答案。但我
will say that when I was I had other
可以说，我当时也有一些其他的
ideas that were interesting to me like
想法，从
intellectually like yeah like this is a
理论上讲，这些想法很有趣，比如，嗯，这确实是个
good idea um but it just didn't hit me
好主意，但它就是没能触动我的
and my heart and I would I would like
内心。我
try to work on it but like I said it
尝试着去实践，但就像我说的，
felt like it felt like doing homework
感觉就像在做作业，
like okay I'll like force myself to work
好吧，我强迫自己去做，
on this but it just wasn't I don't know
但就是不行。我不知道为什么。
and then when the idea for hinge hit me
然后，当Hinge的想法突然出现在我脑海里时，
I don't I just don't know how to
我不知道该怎么
describe it except to say like it it was
形容，只能说它就像
like it like infected me and this this
感染了我，这个
this service this app was like going to
服务、这个应用就像要从我体内诞生一样，
come out of me no no matter what and
无论如何。我
it's like I like was almost possessed to
几乎是被某种力量驱使着去完成它。
have to work on it but I think there was
但我认为，关键在于
the the magic of me being open and like
我保持开放的心态，
thinking about ideas and trying to work
思考各种想法，尝试去实践它们。
then when the right idea hit it almost
然后，当真正合适的想法出现时，我几乎
didn't even feel like a choice like I
感觉不到选择的必要，我
just had to work on this so many people
只需要去做这件事。
have the idea so many people feel
很多人都觉得这个想法很棒，以至于
infected by their belief in that idea
他们被这个想法所感染，
but then the vast majority will be
但绝大多数人却被
incarcerated by fear and you know loads
恐惧所束缚，而且你知道，很多
of naysayers telling them you can't make
反对者会告诉他们，你不可能做
an a dating app what the hell is that
一个约会软件，那是什么鬼东西？是的，
yeah you know which is exactly the
你知道，这正是
feedback that I got by the way like I
我得到的反馈。顺便说一句，我
entered it in the business plan
参加了商业计划
competition we were you know we didn't
比赛，结果一分未得，
place at all we were told like this is a
他们说这是个
horrible idea I wrote a paper on it for
糟糕的想法。我为班级写了一篇关于这个想法的论文，
our class they told me it was a horrible
他们也说这是个糟糕的
idea I um I had friends telling me it
想法。我的朋友们也告诉我这
was a horrible idea I would later try to
是个糟糕的想法。后来我尝试
raise money and VCS would tell me it was
筹集资金，风险投资人也告诉我这是个烂主意。几乎
a hor like everyone was like there was
所有人都觉得，
very little positive feedback I was
我对
getting on the idea for Hing I just had
Hing的想法几乎没有任何积极的反馈。我的
this thesis that if you could make a a
想法是，如果你能做一个没有
dating service that was stigma-free if
歧视的约会服务，如果
you could make something that was really
你能做一个真正
fun and easy and lightweight then young
有趣、简单、轻便的东西，那么
people would use it I we we i' always
年轻人就会使用它。我总是
hear that the dating Market is full it's
听到有人说约会市场已经
saturated this is what VC's would tell
饱和了，这就是风险投资人在
me when I would J raise money like
我筹集资金时告诉我的，比如
match.com owns this Market you'll never
Match.com就拥有这个平台。 市场竞争你永远
be able to beat
无法战胜
them and I remember thinking to myself
他们，我记得当时我在想，
like it's not how could you say a market
怎么能说市场
is sat like I don't I almost know no one
饱和了呢？我几乎不认识任何
who uses dating services like it's not
使用约会服务的人，它根本没
saturated you just have to fix the
饱和，你只需要解决
problem why people don't use it and
人们不使用约会服务的问题。人们不
people don't use it because it it has
使用是因为它带有
stigma to it so we can't remember that
污名，所以我们都忘了这一点。
yeah this generation can't remember that
是的，这一代人忘了以前
internet in fact what's so funny is as
网上约会也曾被污名化。事实上，有趣的是，就像
you said the word stigma I said to
你刚才说的“污名”这个词，我当时就在想，
myself what stigma and I thought and
什么污名？
then I thought back to my childhood and
然后我想起了我的童年，
and I remember the what I thought of
我记得我当时是怎么看待
people that used match.com yeah lonely
使用Match.com的人的——孤独的
weirdos totally and that was definitely
怪人，完全是这样。那绝对是
people that's how people thought about
人们当时的想法，人们就是这么想的。是的，
it yeah in 2011 it was just not you know
在2011年，情况并非如此。你知道，
the iPhone would had just come out a few
iPhone才问世
years ago the App Store was relatively
几年，App Store也相对较
new yeah and people did not meet
新。人们不会
strangers on the internet to go date
在网上认识陌生人去约会，
that was just weird so when did it go
那太奇怪了。那么，约会是什么时候
from Facebook to an
从Facebook变成一个
app uh so we started working on it it
应用程序的呢？ 我们开始着手开发这个项目，它
was originally this yeah Facebook canvas
最初是一个Facebook Canvas
app and that was
应用，那是2011
201122 and um but it was really having
年到2022年。但是，它
trouble getting people to adopt this
很难吸引用户使用。
thing I was not a good product designer
我既不是优秀的产品设计师，
not a good brander it was originally
也不是优秀的品牌塑造者。它最初的名字
called secret agent Cupid it would uh
叫“秘密特工丘比特”，它会把
introduce you to friends of friends but
你介绍给朋友的朋友。
but it was really a complex user
但是它的用户
interface you would like answer
界面非常复杂，你需要回答一些
questions about your friends there were
关于朋友的问题，还有一些排名之类的东西，
like little rankings like it was try to
它试图营造一种
be really social and like show you which
社交氛围，展示你哪些
of your friends are most in demand it
朋友最受欢迎。它包含了很多
had like all these different components
不同的组件，非常
to it it's like way over complicated
复杂。
people would come in and they like
人们打开后会
wouldn't understand like why I'm
不明白，为什么要
answering questions about my friends
回答关于朋友的问题，这
like what's this I'm here to date around
是什么？到
the end of 2012 I'd raised a little bit
2012年底，我从
of money from just like angels and
天使投资人、
friends and family like $100,000 or so
朋友和家人那里筹集了一些资金，大概10万美元左右。但是
we're running out of money not making a
我们资金快用完了，
lot of progress I made the call around
进展也不大。
Thanksgiving I got together with my team
感恩节前后，我和团队聚在一起，
and I was like we just need to start
我说，我们需要从头开始，把
over from scratch let's throw this whole
整个
thing out mobile is the future that's
项目都推翻重来。 移动端是未来，
the app store around this time so let's
应用商店里这类应用越来越多，所以我们决定
redesign it for mobile and let's make it
重新设计移动端应用，让它变得极其
just like dead simple we'll just you
简单。你只需要
connect your Facebook account we'll show
连接你的Facebook账号，我们会给
you a photo you know their age like one
你展示一张照片，显示对方的年龄和一
or two lines about them and then you
两句简介，然后你
just say yes or no are you interested in
只需回答“是”或“否”，你
this person we had literally like two
对这个人感兴趣吗？我们当时
and a half months left of cash to like
只剩下两个半月的资金，要
tear everything down rebuild it from
推倒重来，从头开始重建，
scratch and then take our remaining
然后用剩下的
money and throw a giant launch party in
钱在华盛顿特区举办一场盛大的发布会。
yeah that's it literally took our last
没错，就是这样。我们用最后的
$25,000 and threw a giant open bar party
25000美元在华盛顿特区办了一场大型的开放式酒吧派对，
in DC and you had to download the app to
你必须下载我们的应用才能
get in we had submitted our app to the
参加。我们当时觉得时间很充裕，大概两周时间，就把应用提交给了
App Store with what we thought was like
App Store。App
App Store review times were typically
Store的审核时间通常
like just a couple days at that
只需要几天。结果
point and then a few days go by we don't
几天过去了，我们杳无音信；
hear anything back a week goes by we
一周过去了，仍然没有任何消息。
back uh I start trying to reach out to
我开始尝试联系
like the head of the App Store but no
App Store的负责人，但
one who they don't care I'm like some
没人理会，他们根本不在乎。 我当时就像个
random kid like with a app idea no one
懵懂的小孩，带着个app创意，结果没人接
will return my calls it is now the night
我电话。眼看
before the launch party and we still
发布会就要开始了，我们还没做出
app to launch so I like literally have
app呢！我
like my last $25,000 spent on this
最后25000美元都花在这次
launch party with no app I remember
发布会上了，结果app还没做出来。我记得那天
little co-working space and that night I
晚上，我们有个小小的联合办公空间，我
was just like sitting on the floor like
坐在地上，用
covered up my head in the in my jacket
外套捂着头，
and just crying on the floor thinking
哭了起来，心想：
like wow these last two years have been
天哪，这两年都白费了，
for like nothing I've worked so hard and
我那么努力，
I'm going to launch an app Tomorrow
明天就要发布app了，结果
there's no app store like there's 2,000
App Store还没上线，2000
people are coming and there's no
人要来，
app and then I went home that night and
app却还没做出来。那天晚上我回家，
um woke up the next morning and somehow
第二天早上醒来，
miraculously uh the app had been
奇迹般地，app居然通过了
approved in the App Store and so we had
App Store审核！于是
the party that night
那天晚上我们办了发布会，
2 200 people came they all saw each
来了2200人，大家都在
other using the app the next day people
用这个app。第二天，
we made more matches than we' made in
我们匹配到的用户比之前所有记录加起来都多！
that point and they had to download it
必须下载
to get in they had to download it to get
才能登录，这确实有助于克服人们的偏见。
in and that helped overcome I think you
我觉得你
had to like jump start the stigma
需要先打破这种偏见，
because we had a lot of like the very
因为当时华盛顿特区
like the cool people in the social scene
社交圈里很多很酷的人都来了，他们都
downloading it in front of each other
在彼此面前下载，互相
and talking about it and so the fact
讨论。所以，
that it was like really really dead
它真的非常简单易用，
simple and the fact that everyone saw
而且每个人都看到
each other using it I think like started
彼此在使用，我认为这开始打破了
to like jump start and get over that
这种
stigma problem and then we had like 400
偏见。
people log in the next day and we're
第二天就有大约400人登录，我们当时就惊呆了，
like okay wow 400 people on their own
哇，竟然有400人自己登录了！要知道，在
came in I mean up until that point it
那之前，
users coming into our like little app
我们的小应用用户数量少得可怜。我
like I would i' remember I would like
记得我当时会
sit there and like look at the logs and
坐在那里看日志，看到一个用户登录，然后我们就会想，哦，原来有
okay like a there's a user using the app
个用户在使用这个应用。
and then we like okay he just clicked
然后我们就会想，哦，他刚刚点击了
this button and like then he like passed
这个按钮，然后他就离开了。然后我就只能
like okay wait for the next user to come
等着下一个用户登录，就这么
in like sitting just like watching the
坐在那里看着
logs so hundreds of people coming the
日志。就这样，几百个用户登录了。 第二天来了
next day few hundred more the next day
几百人，第三天又来了几百人，
and then it just started to like build
然后人数就开始不断增长，就像
like a snowboard
滑雪板
effect yeah it really was and and once
效应一样。是的，确实如此。
once we'd hit it with the with the
一旦我们的
product it started to spread through
产品成功推广，它就开始通过
Word of Mouth then people in DC started
口碑传播，华盛顿特区的人开始
to tell their friends in New York and
告诉他们在纽约的朋友，
then we started to build up a weight
然后我们在那里建立了一个客户
list there and then people in New York
名单，纽约的人又
told their friends in San Francisco and
告诉他们在旧金山的朋友，
they would like build a weit list up
他们也在那里建立了一个客户名单。
there and then we would start opening
然后，
cities one at a time once we like we had
一旦我们有
enough liquidity and how would you
足够的资金，我们就开始逐个城市地拓展业务。那么，我们是如何
openin those cities was it the same we'd
拓展这些城市的呢？是不是也一样，我们会
throw another launch party like
举办发布会？
literally my life was just like throwing
我的生活几乎就是
launch parties in cities like we would
在各个城市举办发布会，比如
we would you know from Boston and San
波士顿、
Francisco and um New York and La we were
旧金山、纽约和洛杉矶。
just like I remember 2012 well and there
我记得2012年，那可以说是
apps in a way I remember because we
应用程序的黄金时代。我记得很清楚，因为我们当时在
worked a quite a lot on um on apps back
应用程序方面投入了大量精力，
then and uh there wasn't many apps the
而且当时应用程序并不多，
apps store was was grow felt like it was
应用商店的
growing very quickly I was you know
发展速度非常快。 我们一直在
people were discovering lots of new apps
发现很多新应用，但
all the time feel like people are
感觉
discovering less apps at the moment I
现在人们发现的应用好像少了。我
don't know if that's true or not but I
不知道是不是真的，但我
just felt like that was kind of the app
感觉那段时间像是应用的
boom moment so things like a launch
爆发期。像发布会之类的活动，
party I you know I can see how those
我能理解
things would work then but I I question
当时的运作方式，但我怀疑
now that have got an app and aunch party
现在正在听我讲的人，那些拥有应用和发布会的人，是否真的认为这就能
solve their problems probably not yeah
解决他们的问题。可能未必。很
so interesting and then Tinder around
有意思。然后，Tinder
that time starts to emerge bit bit
差不多就在那时开始出现，对吧？差不多就在
further on right yeah right about that
那时。就在
time so right around the time we threw
我们举办
that launch party I think Tinder had
发布会前后，Tinder 好像在
launched just a couple months prior W
几个月前在
out in La so almost the exact same time
洛杉矶上线了。几乎和
we had a very similar model they took
我们采用非常相似的模式，他们
off hugely and we started to grow as
迅速走红，我们也开始发展壮大。
well in fact their growth helped our
事实上，他们的增长也促进了我们的
growth because it like the category was
增长，因为当时这个类别正在
emerging and now people were like um
兴起，人们开始关注
seeing Tinder and Tinder was a was an
Tinder。Tinder 是一款
app that was all about location and ours
基于地理位置的应用，而我们的应用则
was all about friends of friends and
基于朋友的朋友，
that was really the the main
这才是主要
difference but as a result people viewed
区别。因此，人们把
hinge as like the sort of like more
Hinge 看作是一个更
serious intent dating app because it was
严肃的约会平台。 因为我们的应用是面向
friends of friends people you meet at a
朋友的朋友，也就是你在
house party or dinner or wedding whereas
家庭聚会、晚宴或婚礼上认识的人，而
like the other one was a bit more of
另一个应用则更像是
meeting at a
在
club and as a result all of a sudden the
俱乐部之类的场所结识的，更偏向于更随意的交流。结果，那些之前
VCS who were telling me there's no way
告诉我
this Market's totally saturated now I
市场已经完全饱和的风险投资家们突然改变了看法。我
was no longer begging for money I was
不再苦苦哀求投资，而是开始拒绝那些试图投资的
like Turning Away there people are
人。当时，
around at that point um we went from
我们已经从苦苦哀求众筹，一跃成为
raising almost a $20 million round where
筹集了近2000万美元的融资，
I was turning away money because I just
我甚至都拒绝了他们，因为我真的承受不了更多了。
couldn't take anymore so it really that
这真的
changed the game and was it a straight
改变了游戏规则。但之后的发展是否一帆风顺呢？
there uh no definitely not so we had
当然不是。我们
some good success in 2013
在2013、2014和2015年取得了一些不错的成绩，但
2014 2015 growth started to level out um
增长开始趋于平缓。Tinder
Tinder had definitely gotten successful
无疑取得了巨大的成功，
beat us at the game of like overcoming
在克服用户偏见方面胜过了我们。Tinder
stigma like that it was cool use it was
很酷，它使用起来
was it was quick it was easy it was fun
快捷、方便、有趣。而
ours was just like a
我们的应用只是Tinder的
tender copy that was friends of friends
拙劣模仿，同样是面向朋友的朋友，
but we weren't we were like the growth
但我们的增长速度却慢了下来。 当时
just like wasn't there and um and more
不在场，而且更
importantly though around that time
重要的是，大约在同一时间，《
Vanity Fair called like the dawn of the
Vanit》杂志上发表了一篇文章。  y Fair 杂志称之为约会末日的黎明，文章通篇都在讲述
how dating apps had destroyed dating
约会软件如何摧毁了约会
culture and romance and and hinge was
文化和浪漫，Hinge
featured like pretty heavily in that
在那篇文章里被重点提及。
article and I was remember thinking like
我记得当时我在想，
gosh this is not what I like I built
天哪，这不是我想要的。我创办 Hinge 是
this because I like wanted a girlfriend
因为我想要个女朋友，但这根本
like this is just not what I what I
不是我
wanted to build from like a values
想要的，从价值观的
perspective I I remember going out with
角度来看，这完全不是我想要的。我记得当时我和
my my head of marketing at that time her
市场部主管
name was Katie and I was I was about to
Katie 出去，准备
head home for Thanksgiving and we sat at
回家过感恩节。我们坐在
a little cafe in New York and I I just
纽约一家小咖啡馆里，我跟
was telling her like gosh I I like I
她说，天哪，我真
wish I could just start over from
希望一切从头开始，
scratch like this is not the company I
这不是我
want to build this is not what I want to
想要打造的公司，这不是我想要
do and she's like well I mean you're the
做的事。她说，你是
CEO like what's stopping you I went home
CEO，有什么能阻止你呢？我回家后仔细
and I thought about that and you know
想了想，其实
nothing was stop like what was stopping
没有什么能阻止
me we just raised a big round we had
我，我们刚刚完成了一轮融资，我们有足够的
resources and so uh I decided to reboot
资源。所以，我决定
the company again so we first reboot
再次重启公司。我们在 2012 年进行了第一次重启，
2012 uh this reboot let go of half the
这次重启裁掉了
company and then threw out the old code
公司一半的员工，然后…… 我们放弃了旧的代码
base and built something new from
库，从零开始构建了一个全新的平台，
scratch that would be
旨在
about really helping people who wanted
真正帮助那些想要
to find their person like a long-term
找到另一半的人，打造一个长期
relationship brand and totally change
关系品牌。我们彻底改变了
the user interface and the profiles and
用户界面、个人资料和
the whole flow and design it for people
整个流程，并针对
who actually like really want to find
真正想要找到
their person if you hadn't have had that
另一半的用户进行了重新设计。如果你之前没有
interview with Deborah from
和cafe.com的Deborah进行过那次面试，你
cafe.com before right yeah do you think
觉得
you would have made that decision tell
你会做出同样的决定吗？跟
me about that interview with Deborah
我说说你和cafe.com的Deborah的那次面试，
from cafe.com and how it changed change
以及它如何改变了
things for you so in
你的想法。
2014 someone reached out to me her name
2014年，一位名叫Deborah的人联系了我。
was Deborah and she had downloaded hinge
她下载了Hinge，
she lived in New York and the very first
住在纽约。
person that she that like we suggested
我们给
to her she liked and matched with and
她推荐的第一个人，她就喜欢上了，匹配成功了，
then fallen in love with and so she had
然后就坠入了爱河。于是她
reached out and was like how did you
联系了我，问
like I want to learn more about you I
我感觉怎么样，想更多地了解我们，了解我们的
want to learn about your company we were
公司。当时
just you know we were getting popular in
我们在
New York but not hugely popular so we
纽约已经开始小有名气，但还不是非常受欢迎。有
met up for an interview one day in
一天，我们在
Madison Square Park near my office and
我办公室附近的麦迪逊广场公园见面进行了面试。
um and I you know I didn't have like it
嗯，你知道，这并非偶然，纯粹是运气好。
like the first person that happened to
就像是
show up on her app like we didn't we
她app上第一个出现的那个人，我们真的不是
didn't it was just we were lucky but as
故意的，只是运气好。
we chatted um you know kind of a
我们聊着天，嗯，你知道，就是那种
standard interview at the very end of
标准的面试，快结束的时候
the interview we were getting up and
我们正要起身，
she's like you know one last question
她突然问我最后一个问题，
have you ever been in love and I was
你谈过恋爱吗？我说，嗯，
like well once a long time ago but I you
很久以前谈过一次，但你
know I just didn't realize it until it
知道，我当时没意识到，直到为时已
was too late and Deborah turns off the
晚。黛博拉关掉
tape recorder and she's like listen I
录音机，说，听着，我
have to tell you a story and she tells
得给你讲个故事。她给
me the story of of how actually she sort
我讲了她自己的故事，讲的是她
much younger and they had found each
年轻时遇到的一个人，
other all these years later and realized
后来多年后他们又重逢，意识到
they should have been together and she
他们本该在一起。她说，
was like you know you don't have to make
你知道，你不用犯跟我一样的
the same mistake I did like you can
错误，你仍然可以
still be with the one you just have to
和你的真爱在一起，你只需
do something dramatic you have to just
要做点大胆的事，你需要
go over there and like pour your heart
走过去，敞开心扉，勇敢地表达
out and like put yourself on the line
自己。
and I was like listen lady
我说，听着，女士，
like you know it's been almost eight
你知道，我都快八年没
years since I've even seen her it's it's
见过她了。 感觉一切都结束了，不可能了。当时
way that said I was about to head over
我正准备去
London and I
伦敦参加Hinge的发布派对，
thought okay like I'll just shoot her
心想好吧，那就再给她发条消息吧。
one last note and so I reached out to
于是我联系了
her and I said hey I'm going to be in
她，说：“嘿，我会在
London would love 15 minutes just say hi
伦敦，能不能抽出15分钟跟你打个招呼，
and goodbye it's just weird to think
再见？”想到
that we're never going to see each other
我们以后再也见不到面，感觉很奇怪。
again and she wrote back and she was
她回复说：“嗯，这是我第一次收到她的消息。”然后又过了
another four years
四年，
and uh she was like listen I don't live
她说：“听着，我
in London anymore I live in Switzerland
现在不住在伦敦了，住在瑞士，
but um I'll be around this weekend and
不过这周末我会在附近，很
um happy to hop on the
乐意跟你通个
phone so
电话。”
I like got that message I went to the
我收到消息后就去了
airport I got the I got a ticket to
机场，买了去
Switzerland I got on a plane to Zurich
瑞士的机票，飞到了苏黎世。
and um and she reached out the next day
第二天她又联系了我，说：“
she's like hey I'm around if you want to
嘿，我在附近，想
chat I'm like great cuz I'm going
聊聊吗？”我说：“太好了，因为我
through customs in Zurich right now and
现在正在苏黎世过海关。”
she agreed to meet me at a little cafe
她同意在一家小咖啡馆跟我见面。
and uh we sat down with each other and I
然后，我们坐下来聊了聊。
I think at that time
我觉得当时，一方面
i' you know part of me thought like I
我
really want the girl back like this is
真的很想和她复合，心想这就是我们的缘分吗？
it and part of me thought like it's been
另一方面我又觉得已经
eight years like I've changed so much as
八年了，我变化很大，
a person like I'm sober now I'm like
我现在戒酒了，
running this company like
经营着自己的公司，而
she's with someone else now and by the
她现在有了别人。顺便说一下，当时她
way was literally like a month away from
离结婚只差一个月了，她有
she had a fil she had a fiance yeah and
未婚夫，对，
and to be married in a month like uh so
一个月后就要结婚了，所以她当时就差临门一脚了。
married so I thought we'd see each other
我想我们见面之后，就
like laugh it off and glad we saw each
一笑置之，很高兴能再次见到彼此。说实话，我当时真的
didn't know it was going to happen it's
没想到会这样，
like it felt but there was this hope in
但我心里还是抱有一丝希望，心想：
me that like wow maybe she really is the
哇，也许她真的是我的真命天女，也许
one maybe we'll like realize it and we
我们最终会意识到这一点。我们
sat down at this little cafe and
坐在一家小咖啡馆里，
um and it was just like uh I think we
嗯，我觉得我们都
both felt like an incredible amount of
感觉到了
that connection that we'd always had and
那种我们之间一直存在的奇妙联系。我们
we sat and we we talked for like seven
坐下来，聊了很久。 我
or eight straight hours in this Cafe
在咖啡馆里待了七八个小时，连杯
never even got up to get a coffee and at
咖啡都没起来，
the end of that conversation she's like
最后她突然说
I think I'm calling off the wedding and
她想取消婚礼。然后
so uh about a week later she moved out
大概一周后，她搬出了
of zerk and moved from um back into back
泽克，又搬回了
to New York into my like 300t apartment
纽约，住进了我在西村那间大概300平方英尺的公寓。说了这么
and and my and this is a long way of
多，其实还是回到
getting back to your question which is
你的问题，也就是
like how does this relate to hinge and
这跟Hinge有什么关系，以及
would I have done the reboot because
我会不会选择重启。因为我现在终于找到了
person that I've always want like wanted
我一直想要的那个人，我终于把
like I finally got her back and it was
她追回来了，这感觉
totally amazing
太棒了，大概持续了
for like a month or two or three months
一两个月，或者三个月吧。
maybe Max and then the honeymoon period
然后蜜月期
ended and were two people living in this
结束了，我们两个八年没见的人挤在
little tiny apartment together in New
纽约这间小公寓里，不得不重新了解
figuring each other out and it wasn't
彼此。这并不
perfect and the part of me like I would
完美。
have if I were just dating this person I
如果我只是和她约会，我肯定会直接
would have run right I would have like
跑掉，我会直接结束这段关系，然后说“好吧，她不合适”。 这个
the right person like it's not it's not
人并不像
perfect like I imagined it was going to
我想象的那样完美，
be but she' called off this life she'd
但她放弃了这段感情，
like you know she'd left a her person
你知道，她离开了她生命中最重要的人，
she'd left
她把她的一切都留在了
um her whole existence over there so I
那里，所以我
couldn't just like break up of
不能就这么和她分手。
there and that's when I think the real
我觉得正是在那时，
work of the relationship started and
这段感情才真正开始发展，
real intimacy and vulnerability and like
真正的亲密、脆弱和
love started to form and I realized like
爱开始萌芽。我意识到，
I would have just passed over this
我之前可能就错过了这个
person and I think it just totally
人。这件事彻底
changed my my mentality of how a dating
改变了我对约会
app should be designed because I think
软件设计的看法，因为在
up until that point I thought you know
那之前，我一直觉得约会软件
it's a it's a numbers game you just got
就是个概率游戏，你只需要
to like get through people and once you
筛选掉很多人，一旦
find your person then it's then it's
找到你的另一半，之后就幸福快乐地生活下去了。但我
and realizing that like how many people
意识到，我们认识的很多人，
you know we all must just skate right
我们都因为不够坦诚而直接略过，
past because we don't because we're not
因为我们不够
vulnerable because they're not
脆弱，因为他们不够
vulnerable and we fail to like make that
坦诚，所以我们没能建立起
connection and so I wanted to like
联系。所以我想要
rebuild an app if it were really for
重新设计一个真正用于建立
relationships um you just it would be a
关系的约会软件，它会是一个
very different kind of app you would
完全不同的软件，你必须……
have to like have people slow down you
要让人们慢下来，就
would have to have people be more more
必须让他们更加坦诚，更加敞开心扉，
the line a bit more in order to form
更多地分享自己，承担风险，才能建立
that initial connection and so that was
最初的联系。这就是
design principles for what we wanted to
我们想要
build with a new hinge fairy tale
打造的全新 Hinge 应用的基础和设计原则。童话般的
endings are made for movies because
结局是电影的专属，因为片尾字幕结束后还有
there's a lot of work that happens when
很多工作要做。
totally yeah we were just getting
没错，我们当时才刚刚
started I had no idea and you also when
起步，我对此一无所知。而且，当你
you talk about this new vision for hinge
谈到 Hinge 的新愿景时，你会发现
it's quite idealistic you know this idea
它相当理想化。你知道，我们想要
of just being able to create an app
创建一个应用，让
where people slow down and they give
人们慢下来，提供
more information and they're more
更多信息，更加
vulnerable tends to be the case that
坦诚。但现实往往并非如此，
your ideal scenario for how humans
你理想中的人类
behave isn't actually how they want to
行为模式，实际上并非他们真正想要的
behave right especially these days
行为模式，对吧？尤其是在如今这个时代，
because we're all we all believe things
我们都认为一切都
should be like quick and easy MH and
应该快捷方便，但事实并非如此。付出才有回报。
out what you put in and so we were
所以我们一直在
always fighting this balance of like
努力平衡
what people are willing to do and what
人们愿意做什么和
they should do you know and and we were
他们应该做什么。我们
trying to to like we could of course
当然可以
build an app that's just
开发一个这样的应用。 这就像是让
like makes it like what people think
人们觉得
that they want was like quick and easy
他们想要的是快速、轻松、
and fun but you have to slow people down
有趣的约会方式，但实际上你必须放慢节奏，
get them to put in a little bit more
让他们投入更多
effort and it's a real it's a real
精力。这需要一种真正的
balance of of like getting people to be
平衡，既要让人们尽可能地敞开心扉，又要让他们
vulnerable as much as at least they can
尽可能地保持脆弱。
tolerate and because the more that they
因为他们越是敞开心扉，
are the more effective their experience
他们的体验就越有效，找到另一半的机会也就越大。
received when you come up with this new
当你提出
vision for hinge which is going to be
Hinge的新愿景——
slower much more meaningful and much
更慢节奏、更有意义、
more deeper and really based on forming
更深入，真正基于建立
long-term connections how is that
长期关系——时，
received by people uh I think in theory
人们的反应如何？嗯，我认为理论上是受到
it was it was celebrated right in theory
欢迎的。理论上，
I think people were like yes the world
人们会说，是的，世界
needs this kind of this kind of new
需要这种新
thing like we definitely want something
事物。我们当然想要一些不那么像
food and more like you know a nice
快餐的东西，而更像是一顿
nutritious meal when it comes to dating
营养均衡的约会大餐。
you know it was it was still hard to
你知道，要
really get people like they like it in
真正让人们接受这种理念仍然很难，他们理论上喜欢它，
theory but and they're like wait I have
但实际上，他们会说，等等，我得
to fill out like three prompts like wait
填写三个问题，等等，我
I don't just swipe on people I have to
不能只是滑动屏幕，我得……
like like something about them um wait
比如，
if I like someone they're just going to
如果我喜欢某个人，他们就会
see it like you're just going to tell
看到，就像你会告诉
them I have to add a comment and like
他们我必须添加评论，
say something about them so it was like
说点关于他们的话一样。所以，对于那些习惯了
different but it was effective and
截然不同的方式的人来说，这需要时间去理解，但它确实有效，而
that's What mattered the most and you
这才是最重要的。你
know the that was a it was such a huge
知道，这对
mindset and shift for us to stop
我们来说是一个巨大的思维转变，我们不再
thinking about user engagement and user
关注用户参与度、用户
retention and all these like classic
留存率以及所有那些风
metrics that you know VCS look for when
投公司在
they look at like social media apps and
评估社交媒体应用时会关注的传统指标，而是
to just think are we getting people out
思考我们是否能让人们进行
on more good dates or not and that's
更多优质的约会。这将
going to be our Northstar metric and
成为我们的北极星指标，
we'll grow through word of mouth because
我们将通过口碑传播发展，因为
people are actually going to go on good
人们真的会进行优质的
dates and they're going to tell their
约会，并且他们会告诉他们的
friends about it and so that was our
朋友。这就是我们的
Northstar and so we didn't worry so much
北极星指标。因此，我们不再那么担心
about like all those engagement metrics
那些参与度指标，
and you know we didn't there weren't as
你知道，
many matches and there wasn't as much
匹配数量没有那么多，
whatever engagement on the app it was
应用上的互动也没有那么多，但
actually way more efficient and
实际上，它更高效、更
effective of getting people out on good
有效地让人们进行优质的约会。
dates and so we launched this new thing
推出新产品后，
our user numbers actually started to
我们的用户数量实际上
decline initially from the old version
从旧版
of the app what about money yeah and so
应用开始下降。资金方面呢？是的，差不多就在
right about that time we're starting to
那时，我们
order to build this new app and we're
为了开发这款新应用已经耗尽了所有资金，
starting to run out and so I went out to
开始出现资金短缺。所以我又开始四处
start fundraising again and telling the
筹款，讲述我们的
story of like look at these like we
故事，比如“看看这些，我们
we're way more effective now people love
现在效率更高了，人们喜欢我们的
product but on the other hand we used to
产品。但另一方面，我们以前有
have I don't know at the time 400
40万到
500,000 users and now we're down to like
50万用户，现在却只有10万到
100,000 150,000 users and that's a
15万用户了。这对
pretty tough story to tell to venture
风险
capitalists and but you're shrinking
投资家来说是个很难接受的故事。虽然用户数量在减少，
yeah we're shrinking but but we're gonna
但我们会
grow because look at how amazing these
增长的，因为看看这些多么出色！”
and no one like really bought that story
但没有人真正相信这个故事。
and I was flying around everywhere
我到处奔波，和所有
talking to every VC and I could talk to
我能接触到的风险投资家洽谈。
you know at that point Hing has gotten
你知道，当时Hing已经
popular enough that any VC would like
足够受欢迎，任何风险投资家都愿意和
take my meeting and talk to me but it
我见面，但
was just I probably had 50 or 60 VC
我可能只有50个左右的联系人。 我们参加了60场风投
meetings and like not a single not a
会议，结果一个都没成功。
single yes but at right on that time we
但就在那时，我们
also started talking to um match group
也开始和Match Group洽谈。
they saw they could see what I saw they
他们看到了我所看到的，他们觉得
saw wow this is actually something
这确实
that's different it's differentiated and
与众不同，很有
promise and so when we were down to like
潜力。所以，当我们
once again like days of cash probably
再次面临资金短缺，可能只剩下几天，甚至
like a week or two left of cash we
一两周的现金时，我们和
investment from them that would set the
他们协商了一笔初始投资，这笔投资为
stage for them to eventually acquire the
他们最终收购我们奠定了基础。在
and between 2016 and 2019 when they
2016年到2019年他们
acquired the company what was growth
收购公司这段时间里，公司的发展情况如何呢？
like uh it was slow at first 2016 2017
嗯，一开始比较慢。2016年和2017年，
we were kind of still figuring out the
我们还在摸索，因为
it was a completely new model and so we
这是一个全新的商业模式，所以我们在努力让
that new model work and we were like you
这个新模式真正发挥作用，不断地
know um tuning it and around 2018 we
调整和改进。到了2018年左右，我们
felt like okay we've really started to
感觉
like now people are really starting to
用户开始真正喜欢上
love this app it's starting to really
这款应用，它开始
grow through word of
通过口碑迅速发展。
mouth and and and then we started to
然后我们开始加大
like pour on marketing money and at that
营销投入，那时效果已经
point it was showing like how much that
显现出来了。 这
could accelerate the growth and that's
能加速增长多少？正因如此，
when match group invested hinge Labs
Match Group投资了Hinge Labs。Hinge
what is hinge Labs I don't believe any
Labs是什么？我相信
other dating apps have something like
其他约会应用都没有类似
hinge laabs yeah and it's all part of
Hinge Labs的功能。是的，这都是
this idea that we want to build like
我们想要打造的理念的一部分，我们
we're just focused on user Effectiveness
专注于提升用户体验，确保用户能够真正进行有效的
good dates and a huge piece of the you
约会。你
know a dating app is is relatively
知道，约会应用的一大特点是它相对
unique it's not just a piece of
独特，它不仅仅是一项
technology it's you know what what it's
技术，更重要的是
the people that are on there and how
用户以及
they're behaving and the technology like
他们的行为方式。技术才是
that's your experience as a user it's
用户体验的关键所在。无论
not just like we no matter how good we
我们
get at product and product design or
在产品和产品设计方面做得多么出色，
whatever like we have to control for the
我们都必须控制
behaviors of other people and making
其他用户的行为，
sure that we have the right people on
确保我们吸引的是行为得体的用户。
we can only guide them so much with um
我们只能通过用户体验来引导他们，
you know ux we also have to like kind of
我们还需要指导
Coach people and guide people and teach
用户，帮助
people how to become better daters and
他们成为更好的约会者。
so Hing X or sorry Hing Labs was
因此，Hing X（抱歉，应该是Hing Labs）的
developed to sort of study daters who
开发目的就是为了
are successful study daters who are not
研究成功的约会者。 不成功，
patterns what do we see and how can we
我们无法找出规律，也无法确定我们观察到了什么，以及如何
help level up everyone to become better
帮助每个人提升约会水平，成为更优秀
and more successful daters and so Hing
、更成功的约会者。因此，Hing
Labs really does you know deep dive
Labs 确实会进行深入
research studies on just what is what
研究，探究是什么
makes data successful um and and gives
让数据成功，并为
us the fuel to be able to um build
我们开发
better product or build user guides
更好的产品或用户指南等提供动力。
things like that so what makes data
那么，是什么让数据
successful makes dating successful yeah
成功，约会又如何成功呢？是的，
like you know I've Got Friends that seem
你知道，我有一些朋友
to be successful at dating and friends
在约会方面似乎很成功，而另一些朋友则是
that are just those prolific serial
那种
datas that go on 100 dates a year and
一年约会上百次却
never seem to make any progress yeah and
似乎毫无进展的“数据狂人”。是的，
that you talk about you must have got
你提到的数据类别，肯定也有吧？
like categories like the serial data
比如那些
that's never going to be successful
永远不会成功的“数据狂人”，
they're just doing it for the fun of it
他们只是为了好玩，就像
and they're like one hit wonder we we
昙花一现一样。我们
definitely have different profiles but
当然有不同的用户画像，但
we anytime we try to like just put
每当我们试图将
people into discreet categories it never
人们简单地归类时，都
works because people are complex and
行不通，因为人是复杂的，
they have different everyone's story is
每个人都有不同的经历，每个人的故事都是
kind of unique and so it's hard to put
独一无二的，所以很难把
people just like into
人简单地归类。
buckets um and there I think some
我认为有一些
general principles that I've learned and
普遍的原则…… 我和
we've learned through hinge labs and you
我们都通过Hinge Labs学到了很多，而且你
know again you had Logan here relatively
知道，Logan不久前也来过这里。
recently and if if people are interested
如果有人感兴趣，
they should definitely go listen to her
他们绝对应该去听听她的
podcast because with you because it's
播客，因为她和你一起做的播客简直就是
like a master class and how to become
一堂大师课，教你如何
successful in dating yeah but I would
在约会中取得成功。是的，我
say like the more that you are willing
想说的是，你越愿意
be honest and vulnerable and real like
坦诚、脆弱、真实，
the quicker you can find those
你就能越快找到那些
connections and the higher Quality
联系，而且
Connections that you're going to
你
get I think that's the kind of upshot
获得的联系质量也会更高。我认为这就是最终结果，也是
and the way that we really try to design
我们设计
hinge to help people maximize their
Hinge的初衷，就是帮助人们
success on that
在这方面最大限度地取得成功。
front why does that matter at a human
为什么
level being honest and
坦诚和
vulnerable uh I think two reasons one is
脆弱在人际交往层面如此重要呢？我认为有两个原因。首先，
that you get to an accurate assessment
你可以
more quickly of someone right like if
更快地对一个人做出准确的评估。如果
you're trying to be pretend to be
你试图伪装成另一个
someone you're not or just trying to be
人，或者只是为了
cool or get a lot of likes or whatever
耍酷、博取点赞等等，
people aren't seeing the real you and
人们就看不到真实的你，但
they're going to eventually see the real
他们最终会看到真实的
You So the faster that you can just put
你。所以，你越早
like be clear about who you are and what
清楚地表达自己是谁、
you're looking for and what you want and
你在寻找什么、你想要什么以及
what's not perfect about you then I
你有哪些不足之处，我
think the faster you're going to find
认为就越容易成功。 你越快找到
someone who's like yes this is the type
一个会说“是的，这就是
of person that I want to be and you're
我想成为的那种人”的人，你就能
going to avoid all those people that
避开那些被
that you'd put up but then they get to
你伪装出来的外表所吸引，但当他们
know the real you and then that's not
了解真正的你之后，就会发现并非如此的人。
and then I'd say the second piece is
其次，我认为，这就像给
that it gives people like hooks to grab
人们提供了一个可以抓住的钩子。
about with someone who's perfect and inv
和一个完美无缺、刀枪不入、无所不能的人在一起，根本没什么可聊的。你会问自己：
what do you like what do you have to say
你喜欢什么？你有什么想说的？我们正是通过彼此的
like we connect over the the cracks of
裂痕
and the little imperfections and that's
和小瑕疵来建立联系，这才是我们
how we connect and relate to one another
彼此连接和相处的方式。
and so you'll form a much better and
所以，当你敞开心扉，而不是试图给人留下深刻印象时，你就能
deeper and quicker bond with someone
与他人建立更好、更深刻、更快速的联系。那么，
impress okay what about this then so if
如果
I wanted to be the world's worst
我想成为世界上最糟糕的
data if I wanted to be the world's worst
数据用户，或者更广泛地说，成为世界上最糟糕、
um most unsuccessful hinge user or
最不成功的Hinge用户或
dating app user more generally what
约会软件用户，
would I have to
我该怎么
do uh so I've got your first point which
做呢？嗯，我明白了你的第一点，也
is about be really inauthentic pretend
就是…… 做个很虚伪的人，假装
I'm perfect and use fake photos or you
自己完美，用假照片，或者
just portray myself in a way yeah a lot
只是刻意塑造形象，比如用滤镜拍自己戴着
sunglasses or hanging out with a lot of
墨镜的照片，或者和很多
friends one-word answers to your prompts
朋友一起玩的照片，对问题只用一个词回答，
you know just like everyone or no one or
你知道，就像“每个人都喜欢”或者“没人喜欢”或者“
wait for likes to come to you I think
等着别人点赞”一样。我觉得
they're trying to get people out of we
他们想让人们摆脱这种心态。
want to we want people to like fill out
我们希望人们能更
deeper like that's so much of our work
深入地了解自己，这才是我们工作的重点。我们的大部分工作
is like helping people select better
就是帮助人们选择更能
photos that Shore more their personality
展现他们个性的照片，
help people answer
帮助他们回答
prompts which are these short questions
问题——这些问题是一些简短的，
designed to get you into a conversation
旨在引导你进行对话，
and answer them
并让你认真思考后再回答。认真对待
to uh be really thoughtful with your
你的
life because the more thoughtful you are
生活，因为你点赞越用心，
with your likes the better our algorithm
我们的算法就越精准，
gets because we actually understand who
因为我们能真正了解
you like and who you don't like so don't
你喜欢什么，不喜欢什么。所以不要随便点赞，
just like you know no because then we
因为那样
can't we can't learn your taste right
我们就无法了解你的品味，
and we're not going to get closer and
也无法越来越
closer to the type of person that you
接近你
like okay interesting and what about
喜欢的类型。好的，很有意思。那么
these um these serial datas because I've
这些序列数据呢？因为我
got some friends that are like those
有一些朋友 就像那些
serial datas literally 100 dates a year
连续的约​​会数据一样，一年约会100次，
and I'll sit with them and we'll chat
我会和他们坐下来聊天，
and they'll tell me oh yeah I want three
他们会告诉我“哦，我
dates this week etc for those people I'd
这周想约会三次”等等。对于这些人，我
love to be able to get offer them advice
很想给他们一些建议。我
thinking of one one of my friends in
特别想到我的一个朋友，
particular who I know was is going to
我知道她肯定会
watch this yeah I mean I was one of
看这个视频。是的，我以前也是这样的人，对吧？
those people right I mean I was a person
我以前就是那种人，
um uh you know constantly was I wouldn't
嗯，你知道，我总是……我不是说
necessarily just go on a whole lot of
要去很多次第一次约会，
first dates but I would go on a whole
而是会去很多次
I'd had a whole lot of two to six week
两到六周的
relationships and um and then as soon as
恋爱关系。然后，一旦
I would find something quote unquote
我发现什么“不对劲”的地方，
wrong or I wouldn't feel good in the
或者在恋爱关系中感觉不好，
relationship then I was like well this
我就会想“不行，这样
doesn't work like this is wrong cuz I
不对劲”，因为我
think I had such
觉得我对
a I had such a fantasy about what a good
一段好关系有太高的幻想了，
relationship looked like I like my model
我的模型
was totally broken and I think for so
完全崩坏了。我觉得
many of us we're like we're trying to
我们很多人都在试图把
fit like a model in our head with the
脑海中的模型和
real with the reality that we're trying
现实匹配起来，试图让现实和我们想象的完全一致。 我们每个人
model in our head about what a good
脑子里都有一个关于美好关系应该是什么样子的模型，
I think my model was like you know it
我觉得我的模型是这样的：你知道，每次在一起都充满
stays sexy fun every single time we're
激情和乐趣，
together um we don't fight there's never
我们从不吵架，从来没有……
any you know there's like I I think I
你知道，就像……我觉得我…… 我
after moment in my mind and so I skipped
脑海里一直有个非常美好的“从此幸福快乐地生活在一起”的结局，所以我跳过了
over and passed over so much because it
很多，因为那些
just didn't fit this like model on had
都不符合
of my head and I think some of us have
我脑海中的设想。我觉得我们有些人
models in our head that are exceedingly
脑子里对理想伴侣的设定非常
narrow they have to be like over six
狭隘，比如必须身高超过六
foot and they need to work in this type
英尺，必须从事某种特定的
of job and they need to be like this and
工作，必须符合某种标准。
so you go out and you're just looking
所以当你出去约会时，你总是在寻找
for some reason to say no because it
拒绝的理由，因为对方
doesn't fit your model and I think the
不符合你的标准。我认为最重要的
biggest thing is for us
是，我们要
to um like change the model in our head
改变脑海中对理想伴侣的固有认知，
trying to look for and like widen that
拓宽一下
aperture a bit and give people more of a
视野，给别人更多
chance and like see things through a bit
机会，让他们看得更透彻一些。
thing you mentioned the six-foot thing
你刚才提到的身高问题，六英尺这个标准，
seems to be a lot of conversation
似乎是一个经常被讨论的话题，
because I think the vast majority
因为我觉得绝大多数
people the vast majority of women I
人，尤其是绝大多数女性，都希望
imagine would want someone that's more
找到一个身高
than six foot is that
超过六英尺的伴侣，是这样吗？
correct uh no I don't I don't know if
嗯，我不知道
that's actually true but people like
这是否属实，但人们确实喜欢
someone taller than them tter than them
比自己高的人。
okay yeah
嗯，
um that's just one example I mean I
这只是一个例子。我的意思是，我
don't know about the height but I think
不太了解身高，但我觉得
it's just the point is like we have very
重点是，我们现在的择偶
specific and narrow models and I think a
标准非常具体、非常狭隘。
lot of people who end up in successful
很多最终拥有成功伴侣的人都会
say this isn't you know if I were making
说，这可不是……你知道，如果我列
a shopping list and like you know
一张购物清单，
writing down all my like little features
写下我择偶的所有要求，
that I'm looking for in a partner like
比如
this person didn't
这个人，我未必会符合这些条件，
necessarily that like I would have I
我可能就
would have missed this person there's a
错过了这个人。有个
website isn't there I can't remember the
网站，对吧？我记不清
name of it but you go on there and you
名字了，你可以在上面输入你对
say what you're looking for in a partner
伴侣的要求，
and it shows you your statistical
它会显示你
probability of finding that person okay
找到这个人的概率。
yeah I don't know about that but yeah I
嗯，我不太了解那个网站，但我
think if people saw that it's horrifying
觉得如果人们看到这个结果，会
yeah be pretty horrifying like how
很可怕。真的会很可怕，就像
you're cutting out 98% of people um
你
based on your criteria the salary the
根据自己的标准——薪水、
height the weight um the race you put on
身高、体重、种族等等——排除掉了98%的人，
there and then it shows you it goes like
然后它会显示你
you have a 0.0% chance of finding this
找到这个人的概率是0.0%，对吧？
person right um and you obviously you
而且你显然
want them to be single as well as
希望对方是单身。 还有
another criteria um which I find
一个我觉得很
interesting one of the things people say
有意思的标准，就是人们常说的
about dating apps and like dating app
关于约会软件、约会软件
companies and Founders and CEOs is they
公司、创始人以及CEO们的一点：他们
want people to stay single because then
希望用户保持单身，因为这样才能
you've got more customers and surely if
有更多用户。当然，如果
people are becoming um are getting
用户
married you're losing
结婚率高，用户就会流失。
customers yeah so our belief on that
所以我们一直以来都坚信这一点，我们的
motto our our tagline is designed to be
座右铭/标语是“旨在被
deleted and that came from by the way we
删除”。这源于我们当时和
were working with a branding agency and
一家品牌代理公司合作，他们问我们：“你们的特色是
they were like what's hinges stick you
什么？是
know like what makes you different like
什么让你们与众不同？
you're Tinder but what and I was like I
你们是Tinder，但又是什么？” 我说：“
don't there's no gimmick like there's no
没有噱头，没有‘
like oh we're Tinder but like X or
我们是Tinder，但有X’或者‘
Tinder but y like every single part part
Tinder，但有Y’之类的东西。我们应用的每一个部分都经过精心
of the app is like designed to be
设计，旨在
different and like designed to help get
帮助
people out on great
用户找到美好的
dates and that's kind of where this like
约会对象。” 这就是“旨在
designed to be deleted which by the way
被删除”这个标语的由来。顺便说一句，我们
internally about that because it's so it
内部对此有很多争论，因为它
sounds so technical like design like in
听起来很专业，就像“
your own tagline like designed to be
设计”这个词出现在你们自己的标语里一样。 就像
like and it people won't understand it
这样，人们可能不会理解，
but we kind of went with it because it's
但我们还是坚持了下来，因为这是
the only thing that really represented
唯一真正代表
what makes hinge um really different
Hinge与众不同的地方。这
what do that mean and it means that do
意味着什么呢？这意味着我们能否帮助
we get people out on great dates or not
人们找到很棒的约会对象。
and that's what's Driven every design
这正是我们所有设计
decision and why hinge looks different
决策的驱动力，也是Hinge与
than all the other apps is like that
其他应用截然不同的原因——
optimization function and so in terms of
优化功能。在
a business model the belief is that like
商业模式方面，我们相信
we will grow through Word of Mouth which
口碑传播能够带来增长，这
is the most effective and efficient and
是最有效、最
cost- effective way to grow if we just
经济的增长方式。如果我们能
create more great dates and more
创造更多美好的约会和更多
relationships and the thesis is like as
关系，就能实现增长。我们的理念是，
long as there are single people in the
只要世界上还有单身人士（
world which I'm pretty sure there are
我相信现在
plenty of single people left in the
单身人士仍然很多），
world that they'll want to use h which
他们就会想要使用Hinge。Hinge更像是
feels more like a utility that's truly
一个真正有效的实用工具，而不是像
game since the company started have you
游戏一样的东西。自公司成立以来，您是否
seen any changes in the dating
观察到约会
environment the dating landscape dating
环境、约会格局或约会
culture yeah gen Z for lack of a better
文化发生了任何变化？是的，Z世代（暂且这么称呼吧）的
term has different dating patterns I
约会模式有所不同。我
think in some sense like when I started
认为，在我创立
hinge people were there was a lot of
Hinge的时候，人们
stigma around dating apps because
对约会应用有很多偏见。 因为
um uh people just didn't use them at all
嗯，嗯，以前人们根本不用它们，
then I feel like everyone started
后来我觉得大家开始都
started to use them and it became sort
用了，它逐渐成为了一种
of the default way to meet people and I
默认的交友方式。我
think this is why we've actually like
认为这就是为什么
hing's growth has accelerated so much
Hing 的增长如此迅猛，
even recently is that there actually is
甚至最近也是如此的原因：
that's people are willing to share more
人们渴望摆脱那种快速、肤浅的滑动式交友，转而使用一种更愿意分享
about themselves and be more like I
自我、更坦诚的方式。我
think like genz is generally willing to
觉得 Z 世代普遍更愿意展现
being vulnerable putting yourself out
脆弱的一面，就像 TikTok 而不是 Instagram 那样，你
there you don't have to look so polished
不需要看起来那么完美无瑕，
and so perfect and that's actually great
那么光鲜亮丽。这对于约会来说其实很棒，
for for uh dating because that's exactly
因为这正是
the kind of ethos that we actually need
我们需要的，
for people to be
人们才能
successful and hinge as I was reading is
成功。我读到 Hing
got these sort of five first
有五项基本
principles what is the um current
原则，那么它目前的
company mission
公司使命
statement well so the we want to Foster
宣言是什么呢？我们希望促进
intimate connection to create a less
亲密关系，创造一个不再
lonely world
孤独的世界。
and a lot of social we'll call them like
很多社交平台，我们称之为
social networks they started social
社交网络，它们最初就是从社交
networks were also I think had a similar
网络发展而来的。 我认为我们和你们有着相似的
Mission like you wanted to get you
使命，都希望帮助用户与
connected to the people who matter most
最重要的人建立联系。但
they all became social media companies
他们最终都变成了社交媒体公司，
instead because it turns out that like
因为事实证明，
Brands and influencers and outrageous
品牌、网红和那些特立独行的
people are just more interesting than
人比
your friends and it's easier to get you
你的朋友更有趣，更容易让你
to spend more time in app and more time
在应用上花费更多时间，花更多时间
looking at ads if we like show you much
看广告。如果我们向你展示
more sensation content than than like
更多耸人听闻的内容，而不是
you know real um like creating real
真正
moments of connection with the people
与
who matter most to you and that's what I
你最重要的人建立联系，就能让你更长时间地沉迷其中。这正是我
wanted to drive home like really clearly
想要强调的，也是
in our mission is that like hinge at its
我们使命的
core even if we were expanded in new
核心。即使我们未来拓展到新的
business lines or do something in the
业务领域或做其他事情，我们仍然是一家致力于建立
intimate connection about onetoone deep
亲密联系、一对一深度
connections between people and we don't
联结的公司。我们永远不会
ever want to deviate from that as our
偏离这个
core because it's really what the world
核心，因为这正是
needs right now first principle two
当今世界所需要的。第一原则，第二原则，彻底
radical trust so you've got designed to
信任。所以，
yeah which means so radical trust Is our
彻底信任是我们的
commitment to and so these cultural
宗旨。
principles that you're reading off came
你现在读到的这些文化原则都
from this book um called how we do
来自一本书，叫做《我们如何
things and so when I when we rebooted
做事》。 所以，在2015年底到2016年初我们重启
the company in
公司的时候，我当时根本
2016 we um at that point I didn't think
没考虑过
about company culture kind of at all it
公司文化。我们当时只有30个人，大家
was just like just we bunch of people in
聚在
a room trying to solve problems like
一个房间里，努力解决问题，所以公司文化就
culture just kind of emerges naturally
自然而然地在
among that group of people it really
这些人中间形成了，它主要围绕
rotates around the founder but I didn't
创始人展开。但我当时并没有刻意去想这个问题。
it when we did that reboot we we let go
重启的时候，我们裁掉了
of half the company we took the
公司一半的员工，留下了
remaining half and we went and did an
剩下的一半，然后我们进行了一次非
offsite and we did a a breakdown and a
现场会议，进行了一次彻底的分析，进行了
really had like some really honest at
一些非常坦诚的
times tearful conversations about like
对话，有时甚至到了流泪的地步，讨论我们哪里出了问题，哪些地方
what had gone wrong what did we do right
做得对，哪些地方做得
what what didn't we do right right what
不对，哪些地方
do we wish we had done better um and a a
我们希望做得更好。
lot of them were of course like product
当然，很多问题都和产品
decisions like oh we focus too much on
决策有关，比如我们太关注
the competition and copying the
竞争对手，抄袭
competition and not focusing enough on
竞争对手，而忽略了
customer but a lot of it was like how we
客户。但很多问题都和我们
operated as a company and coming out of
公司的运营方式有关。在那之后，
that we actually started a like
我们实际上启动了一个
open-source Google doc that listed our
开源的谷歌项目。 这份文件列出了我们对 Hing 的
kind of what we believed and how we
信念以及我们
think things should should get done
认为事情应该如何围绕
around hinge and originally it was just
Hing 进行。最初，它
like a long dock of just all kinds of
就像一个长长的清单，列出了各种各样的
principles it was me just trying to like
原则。我只是想把
put my management algorithm like down
我的管理算法写下来，写在
and on a piece of paper so that everyone
一张纸上，让每个人都
was very clear about how I made
清楚地知道我是如何做
decisions and how we should all make
决定的，我们应该如何做
decisions and how we should prioritize
决定，我们应该如何确定优先级
and what we should do so then eventually
以及我们应该做什么。后来，
as Hing got a little bit bigger and we
随着 Hing 的规模扩大，
employees that model didn't make as much
员工人数超过 100 人，这种模式就不再
sense anymore and we put it in this book
适用了。我们把它整理成了一本书，
called How we do things which was at
叫做《我们如何做事》，这本书当时
that point just a list of all our lesson
只是我们所有经验教训的清单。
it's really about it's a story of our
它实际上是一个关于我们
lessons learned it's like we did it all
吸取教训的故事，就像我们曾经用
the wrong ways and that led us to learn
错误的方式做事，而正是这些错误引导我们学会了用
to do it the right way and so that's
正确的方式做事。这就是这些
these principles came from so designed
原则的由来。
to be deleted was like we used to focus
我们过去过于关注
on the competition and focusing on like
竞争对手，关注他们
what features our competitors had when
有哪些功能。但在
we did the reboot we just focused on you
我们进行调整后，我们只专注于
know making our one metric getting
一个指标：让
people out on great dates and I like
用户拥有良好的约会体验。
prohibited people from looking at the
禁止员工查看
competition I didn't want any of their
竞争对手，我不想
apps on my phone like I just just focus
在手机上安装他们的任何应用程序，我只想专注于为
customer radical trust was about a lot
客户提供服务的创新。彻底信任意味着很多
of the decision making was like very top
决策都是自上而下的，
down and um and I think people felt
嗯，我认为人们感到
disempowered they felt a lot of Whiplash
无能为力，感觉像是被鞭打了一样。
and radical trust was about how do you
彻底信任意味着如何
push decision- making down to the front
将决策权下放到
lines and how do you Empower people with
一线，如何赋予员工
the information that they need so I have
所需的信息。因此，我
a lot of transparency from the top down
从上到下都保持着高度的透明度，让员工了解
about like where we are as a business
我们作为一家企业的现状、
what our needs are what our problems are
需求和问题，
so that people on the front lines can go
以便一线员工能够去
solve it love the leap love the leap is
解决这些问题。我喜欢“飞跃”
this idea that small incremental
这个理念，它认为小的渐进式
optimizations can be can be great but
优化固然很好，但
real uh the the things that matter
真正重要的事情
require like a level of um a much bigger
需要更大幅度的
Innovation leaps and we have to not be
创新飞跃。我们不能
afraid of failure because when you make
害怕失败，因为当你进行
those much bigger Innovation leaps a lot
这些更大的创新飞跃时，很多尝试当然
of them like won't of course land or you
不会成功，或者
have to I think even more importantly
更重要的是，你必须经历
trudge through a whole lot of failure to
大量的失败才能
finally get to success I think there's a
最终获得成功。我认为这
culture of like that comes from people
源于一种文化。
especially who have worked in tech
尤其是那些在科技
companies and much larger tech companies
公司，甚至是规模更大的科技公司工作过的人，他们往往习惯于
of like oh you just test and iterate
测试和迭代，
like you test this thing and then if it
比如测试这个功能，如果有效就
works great and then if it doesn't then
很好，如果无效就继续尝试下一个。
next thing I I think the difference
我认为
between that and then the way that like
这和
often a Founder an entrepreneur will
创始人/创业者通常的思维方式截然不同。创始人/创业者常常会说：“
think is like I believe in this thesis
我相信这个理论，
and I'm going to get there no matter
无论如何我都要实现它。” 想想看，为了
to eventually get to the successful
最终成功开发出
hinge if I just been like oh I'm
Hinge，我经历了多少次迭代？如果我只是
thinking about building a dating app
随便做一个约会应用，然后发布一个版本，
I'll throw something out there and see
看看
if people use it oh gosh they're not
人们是否使用，结果发现没人
really using it I guess the dating app's
用，那约会应用可能就
not a good idea I'll go like build a you
不是个好主意了，然后我就去做其他东西，比如
know whatever uh a car hailing app you
叫车应用。你
have to like trudge through that so
必须经历这些艰难的过程。这就是所谓的“
that's love the leap is like you have to
飞跃”，你必须
suffer through a lot of failure to make
经历大量的失败才能实现
like the big innovation leaps do you see
重大的创新飞跃。你有没有注意到，
a variance and even your team members
即使是你的团队成员，
but other people you work with they're
或者其他与你共事的人，他们也
biased towards failure they're at
倾向于失败？ 他们对
they're different failure appetites yeah
失败的容忍度各不相同，而且随着公司规模的扩大，难度也会越来越大，
and it gets harder and harder as you get
因为你要
fighting against the larger cultural
对抗的是更大的文化
inertia like and it's is very Human by
惯性。顺便说一句，
the way to like not make mistakes and
不犯错、
not um look bad and that's why by the
不让自己看起来很糟糕是很人之常情。这就是为什么
way this whole book is written is like
这本书的写作方式是：把我们
here's all the mistakes that we made and
犯过的所有错误以及
how we did it all wrong just to give
我们做错的地方都列出来，只是为了让
people the permission to know like we're
人们明白，我们都在不断进步，都在努力
learn um so you are overcoming like a
学习。所以，你要克服的是
much larger cultural inertia to get
更大的文化惯性，让
people to take risks and and make
人们敢于冒险，敢于
mistakes how'd you do
犯错。你是怎么做到的？
that uh you exhibit failure from the top
你从高层开始展现失败。
like you admit I think when you've when
你承认，我认为，当你犯错的时候，
like when you've made mistakes like when
就像
I've made mistakes or even talking about
我犯错的时候，或者谈到
you know my development plan or things
我的发展计划或
that I'm working on I just think it like
我正在做的事情时，我认为
you almost all of these cultural
几乎所有这些文化
attributes have to be modeled from the
特质都需要从
top Super interesting because most
高层开始树立榜样。这非常有趣，因为大多数
people are just incentivized to just do
人的动力仅仅是做好
their job so when you bring along a new
自己的工作，所以当你提出一个新
idea or a new innovation you know
想法或一项创新时，
incentive structures mean listen I'm not
激励机制就会发挥作用。 结构意味着，听着，我可不是为了冒这种
getting paid to take that [__] risk
该死的风险才去冒险，
and then be be made to look stupid yeah
然后让自己看起来像个傻瓜的，
so I'm not doing that yeah I think
所以，我不会那样做。是的，我认为
that's right and that's why I think
没错，这就是为什么我认为
we're and we're continuing to evolve
我们正在不断发展和
these principles and and and refine them
完善这些原则。
in fact we're going through a process
事实上，我们现在正在经历一个过程，
right now it's kind of ironic because
这有点讽刺，因为
we're walking through these and I'm
我们正在经历这些，而我
about to release a new version of these
即将向公司发布一个新版本，其中包含
to the company and there has been a bit
一些
of a refinement and we're actually kind
改进，我们实际上正在
of changing this one and combining it
修改这个版本，并将其
with the first one to call it love the
与第一个版本合并，称之为“热爱
problem because so much of about what
问题”。因为
we're really trying to get across
我们真正想
through this is that you have to go like
通过这个版本传达的很多信息是，你必须
really deep and develop a deep thesis on
深入研究，对问题进行深入的探讨，并形成深刻的理论。
a problem and that's what you do I think
我认为，
at this stage of a company you don't
在公司发展的这个阶段，你不再会根据
intuition of a Founder anymore you like
创始人的直觉进行大胆的冒险，而是会对
do deep research on a problem you get
问题进行深入的研究，对它
conviction around it and then you're not
充满信心，然后你不会害怕一次又一次地
afraid to like fail again and again
失败，
trying to solve that problem because you
因为你
are convinced that it's a real problem
确信这是一个真正的问题。
and you understand a lot about it and
你对它了解很多，并且
you're making a very informed decision
正在做出非常明智的决定，
you're taking a very thoughtful approach
你采取了非常周全的方法
to solving it number four was and it
来解决问题。第四点是，它
currently is on my iPad here Guided by
现在就在我的iPad上，是“以原则为指导”，这一点
principles and that one's definitely
肯定会
staying and that's one of the biggest
保留，而且是
uh my own personal journey and I would
我个人经历中最重要的一点。我
say like this journey it just it's sort
想说，这段经历就像
of what I talked about when I talked
我之前谈到
about how this got created in the first
它是如何诞生的一样，
place is that if you keep making the
如果你不断重复
same mistakes over and over again and
同样的错误，并且
you're not having an honest self
不对
assessment about where you are and how
自己的现状和
things are working you won't get better
事情的进展进行诚实的自我评估，你就不会进步。
and so both of my own personal journey
所以，我个人的经历，
and this has happened through you know
以及我从
recovery through alcohol and addiction
酒精和成瘾中恢复过来，
and getting better and better as
并作为
entrepreneurs like I was always
企业家不断进步的过程，都是如此。我一直在进行
self-reflecting and thinking about like
自我反思，思考，比如，
okay like seeking feedback like what
寻求反馈，哪些地方做得不好，哪些地方做得好，
there how can I do that better next time
下次我该如何做得更好。
and it became like I said too arduous
就像我说的，要把
for me to even to track all these things
所有这些事情都记
in my mind so I started putting them in
在脑子里对我来说太费力了，所以我开始把它们写进
that Google doc so that everyone at the
谷歌文档里，这样
company could hold me accountable to
公司的每个人，包括管理层，都可以监督我。
this like management algorithm I was
我当时正在
developing and what I wanted us is to do
开发一种算法，我希望我们
as a company is always make decisions
公司始终
based on principles like what's the
基于原则做决策，比如探究决策的
underlying reason like if I'm making a
根本原因。如果我做出一个
decision no one should ever think well
决定，任何人都不应该认为“
that's just because Justin likes it that
这只是因为贾斯汀喜欢这样做”，
way or that's just because some other
或者“这只是因为
leader at the company that's just what
公司里的其他领导想要这样做，
they want so let's just do it their way
所以我们就按他们的方式来”。
we want people to think like to
我们希望人们思考并
understand like how am I making those
理解“我是如何做出这些
decisions what's underneath that what
决定的？背后的原因是什么？
principles do I believe in that made me
我信奉哪些原则才让我
to choose this over that because if you
选择这个而不是那个？”因为如果你
make that really explicit and clear then
把这些原则明确地表达出来，就能
you gain trust people understand like
赢得信任。人们会理解你
why you're making the decisions and two
为什么做出这些决定，而且
they can start making decisions on their
他们也能开始独立做出决定，而
own without you needing to be in the
无需你
room and start developing their own
在场，并开始发展他们自己的决策
principles for how they make decisions
原则。所以
and so so many of our meetings start off
我们的很多会议都是从“
with like well here are the principles
以下是
that we sort of aligned on as we started
我们开始
to make you know think about this body
思考这项
of work and it just aligns everyone on
工作时达成共识的原则”开始的。这些原则让每个人都对
core set of assumptions and beliefs and
核心假设、信念和
values that we have before we get into
价值观达成一致，然后再深入探讨
the details of the work and that kind of
细节。 工作
counteracts the whole CEO because I said
本身就有点抵消了CEO的作用，因为我说过，
so you know Vibe which might get I guess
你知道，氛围或许能
um might get compliance but it probably
带来合规性，但它可能
won't deliver upon whatever someone
无法实现人们
calls leadership yeah it's not scalable
所谓的领导力。是的，它不具备可扩展性。
and maybe some CEOs always know the
也许有些CEO总是知道
right thing to do but I don't always
该做什么，但我并不总是
know the right thing to do do I I think
知道该做什么。我认为，
my job once we got past 20 or 30 people
一旦我们的员工超过20或30人，我的工作就变得不一样了。顺便说一句，
thing to do even when we were that small
即使在我们规模很小的时候，我也不知道该做什么，
but I thought I did um but as we got
但我当时以为自己知道。但是随着公司规模的扩大，
much bigger like I can't be close enough
我无法掌握足够的
to the to the information to like make
信息来做出
really great decisions and so my job
真正明智的决策。因此，我的
primarily is is building and fostering
主要工作是建立和培育一种能够做出正确决策的企业
the culture that makes good
文化。
decisions I've been thinking a lot about
我一直在思考
comedy culture and I threw this at Brian
喜剧文化，
chesky when he was here this idea of how
当Brian Chesky来这里的时候，我向他提出了这个问题：如何
you create company culture like how do
创造企业文化？如何
you decide I think some people think
决定？我认为有些人认为，
especially post pandemic which caused
尤其是在疫情之后，疫情促使
all of these companies and businesses to
所有这些公司和企业
start thinking about what their company
开始以
culture was in a new way MH you'd see
一种新的方式思考他们的企业文化。你会看到
CEOs and
CEO和
managers almost like brainstorming a
经理们几乎是在集思广益，探讨一种
principlist culture and it was more like
原则主义文化。 更像是问
how what days do you want people to come
你想让员工哪几天来上班，
in Mondays and Wednesdays should we say
周一和周三？还是
two days a week one day a week should we
每周两天？每周一天？
you know um and that just doesn't feel
你知道，嗯……总之感觉不太
right it doesn't feel like it's based on
对劲，感觉没什么依据。
anything so I said to Brian I said one
所以我跟布莱恩说，我在
of the things I'm thinking about is
想，
maybe cult is already there and you just
也许文化本身就已经存在了，你只需要从
the problem you're trying to solve in
你试图解决的问题出发进行逆向工程。
the world which means for example if we
比如说，如果我们
want to be the best dating app in the
想成为世界上最好的约会应用，
world then there's a set of behaviors
那么
we're going to have to exhibit to get
我们就必须展现一系列行为才能实现这个目标，这需要
there which is going to require a set of
一套
values and then with those values we're
价值观。然后，我们会
going to use those values to create
用这些价值观来创建
systems processes and hire the people
系统和流程，并招聘
that we need and so you can almost
我们需要的人才。所以，你几乎可以
reverse engineer your mission as a
逆向工程你的
company um backwards to figure out what
公司使命，从而弄清楚
your culture
你的文化
is you said something about like you're
是什么。你刚才说，你
just describing the culture that already
只是在描述已经
exists and I think that's kind of true
存在的文化，我觉得这有点道理，
especially if you do it early enough
尤其是在你足够早的时候，在
where it's not out of control yet um
它还没有失控的时候，在
when it's like relatively close around
它还相对围绕
the founder you've only got like 30 or
创始人的时候。 如果你只有三四十人或者
40 or 50 people then you definitely have
五十个人，那肯定会形成
some sort of culture and at that point
某种文化。
though I think you want to start
但我觉得到了那个时候，你应该开始
defining defining it so that everyone's
明确定义它，让每个人都
clear on what it is because it will
清楚它是什么。因为
start you'll start losing is it starts
随着规模
expanding and people start it's a game
扩大，就像传话游戏一样，文化
will get lost over time so you want to
会逐渐消失。所以你需要
get really clear on like what it is I
非常清楚地定义它是什么。我
think it's the the best of what is as
认为，它应该体现出最好的一面。
well right because I think you're you're
因为你需要清晰地表达出我们状态
our best this is how we're acting and
最好的时候是什么样的，状态
when we're at our worst this is how
最差的时候又是什么样的。
we're acting because both are always
因为这两种情况
happening within a company like and you
在公司里总是存在的。
don't want to you want to constantly
你不想不断地
prune away the stuff that's not that's
剔除那些不好的东西，让
sort of not great and start having more
更多的
on people replicate what is great so
人去复制那些好的东西。所以，这
it's that it's more like a pruning
更像是一个精简的
process and not just like a here's our
过程，而不是简单地
culture like describe it and put it out
描述一下我们的文化就一股脑地发布出去。
the door but you on the other hand you
但另一方面，你也
can't just like throw it up on a wall
不能…… 就像把它贴在墙上，
and invent it from scratch like once an
然后从零开始创造一样。一旦一个
organization is Big you can't just say
组织发展壮大，你就不能说
like our culture suddenly is going to be
我们的文化突然变成
X Y and Z it'll be so inauthentic to
X、Y、Z，那样会与
what's actually going on on the ground
实际情况严重脱节，根本
that no one would ever follow it I
没人会遵守。我甚至
almost think about like parenting in a
觉得这有点像育儿，
way like you can tell a kid a rule or
你可以告诉孩子一条规则，或者
tell a kid like a but you always have to
告诉孩子一些事情，但你必须时刻
be watching and like giving those little
观察，时不时地给予一些
guidances like here and there you always
引导。
when you when you see people acting with
当你看到人们的行为
in accordance with the culture and
符合文化规范时，要给予
praising it or not in accordance with
表扬；如果不符合，也要
the culture and giving them constructed
给予建设性的
feedback because it's such it's this
反馈。因为文化就像一个鲜活的
living breathing thing like defining it
生命体，很难定义。
is just like one one step but a very
就像迈出了一步，但却是非常
important step and as the company grows
重要的一步。随着公司的发展壮大，
and scales I was thinking about this
我一直在思考“
idea of um the best of what
最好的状态是什么”这个问题。
is when there's 10 of you and you're
当公司只有10个人，甚至
potentially sleeping under a table like
可能像刻板印象里那样睡在桌子底下时，最好的
the right culture for when there is like
状态是否仍然适用于
200 of you yeah totally and you know the
200人规模的公司？没错，完全正确。你知道，
the book you're reading from right now
你现在读的这本书
is when we were you know 50 to 100
是我们50到100
people and and now we're 300 and
人的时候写的，而现在我们有300
something people and and we're evolving
多人了，我们正在不断改进，
them and we're actually changing some of
实际上也在改变一些做法，
them because I've learned things over
因为随着
time that like no longer work at a
时间的推移，我意识到有些做法在
company this big I'll give you an
这么大的公司里已经行不通了。举个
example one is that idea of radical
例子，比如
trust which we just talked about which
我们刚才讨论的“彻底信任”理念，
actually kind of pained me to talk about
其实我谈这个话题有点难受，
because
因为
that's not I've learned that's like not
我发现它不再适合
right for a company this big
这么大的公司了。
anymore you want to push decision-making
你需要把决策权
down somewhat but if you do it too much
下放一些，但如果下放过度，
especially in a larger organization you
尤其是在大型组织里，就会
start getting like a lot of silos and
出现很多部门壁垒，
everyone just doing micro optimizations
每个人都…… 进行微优化，
and there's there's you actually want to
而你真正想要的是，
be there needs to be much more of a
需要进行更多
conversation and actually watch the the
对话，最好看看
the Brian interview and he talks about
布莱恩的采访，他谈到了将
pulling decision- making in and that
决策权下放，
actually is I think more in line with
我认为这才是
stay Innovative and still think like a
保持创新、
startup even at a big scale so there's
即使规模很大也依然保持创业思维的正确做法。有些
things that I took for granted because
事情我以前想当然了，因为在
when we were a 100 people that was
我们只有100人的时候，这些就已经
happening already but I didn't see it
发生了，但我没注意到，
because I just had I knew everyone's
因为我认识每个人的
name we were all in the same room and so
名字，我们都在同一个房间里，所以
there was a lot of CEO and executive
CEO和高管
team influence on the team that that was
团队对团队的影响很大，这种影响是
kind of hidden because it just happened
隐藏的，因为它自然而然地发生了。
naturally so we thought we were pushing
所以我们以为我们已经把
decision- making down however I was I
决策权下放了，但实际上，我一直在
was in conversation with Junior
和初级
developers and Junior engineers and
开发人员、初级工程师和
Junior designers all the time giving
初级设计师交流，提供一些有用的
like little nuggets of feed like I was
建议，就像
like I was involved just not
我参与其中一样，只是没有
officially and I think as we got much
正式参与。随着公司规模的扩大，
bigger we realized like oh gosh you
我们意识到，天哪，你
can't just like push decision- making
不能只是把决策权
down and like hope for the best you have
下放，然后祈祷一切顺利，你必须把决策权下放，让
to like pull it people in and coordinate
大家参与进来，协调一致，
and there are people at the top that
而且还有很多人…… 高层需要
have a view across what's going on
了解
across the whole company that need to
整个公司的运作情况，并
actually be making decisions we can't
做出实际决策，我们不能把决策权
just like push it down just to be super
下放。这一点
clear on that for someone who is you
对于刚入职一个月的创业者来说尤其重要，因为这意味着要
empowering people to make decisions but
赋予员工决策权，但
those decisions coming again through the
这些决策最终都要以
central lens of the company's Mission
公司使命为核心。
when you're really small it's it's it's
当公司规模很小的时候，这种机制就已经
happening already right if you're if
存在了。如果
you're a team of 10 people or 12 people
你有一个10人或12人的团队，
like you're all aware of what each other
你们彼此了解对方的工作，互相
are doing you're talking and you're
沟通，并且会保持
being conscious about if I'm the
清醒的认识。比如，如果我是市场
marketing person and and the product
营销人员，而产品
person over here working on this product
经理正在开发某个产品
feature I I'll think like oh I should
功能，我就会想，哦，我应该
probably Market that product feature
推广这个产品功能。大家对正在发生的事情都有一种
understanding of what's going on so you
共识，就像一个
are making you're like kind of a hive
集体
mind
智慧，
you just take that for granted and as
你对此习以为常。但随着公司规模的扩大，
you get much bigger you can either make
你可能会走向
you know I think the extremes are you
极端，
you just have like a Founder who makes
比如创始人包揽
all the decisions everything just gets
所有决策。 把这些都
brought into them which I think makes a
纳入进来，我认为这会让
lot of people feel disempowered but in
很多人感到无能为力。但
the other hand you push decision- making
另一方面，你又把决策权
completely down you say you all just
完全下放，说你们都来
handle it I'll just articulate the high
处理，我只会阐述
level vision and strategy and you but
高层愿景和战略，然后你们就自己处理。但这样一来，
then you usually don't make great sort
你通常不会做出那种
interdisciplinary or major cohesive
跨学科的、重大的、具有
leaps that are that feel cohesive
凝聚力的飞跃。
everything starts like so it's this
一切都始于此。所以，关键在于保持一种
balance of having just like a constant
平衡：一方面，要有持续的
conversation opportunity for feedback I
对话机会来获得反馈；另一方面，
still ultimately the decision makers of
最终的决策者仍然是那些与
the people who are close to the work
工作密切相关的人。
however we are like pulling it in and
然而，我们也要把这些意见纳入进来，
articulating strategy and and generating
阐明战略，并引发
conversation I'm in the room with more
讨论。坦白说，我现在和更多的
Junior people a lot now than I frankly
初级员工待
continually um bring people along what
在一起的时间比以前多得多，这样我们才能不断地让大家了解
the strategy is what are the big leaps
战略是什么，
we're making and what are all the little
我们正在取得哪些重大突破，以及
ways that we keep this
我们保持
cohesive it's interesting because in the
凝聚力的各种小方法。这很有意思，因为在
age of the internet um and the age of
互联网时代，在
dating apps and all these other tools
约会软件和所有这些工具
and
和
Technologies even though we have better
技术的时代，即使我们的
internet connections the stats continue
网络连接更好了，统计数据仍然
to show that we're getting lonelier and
显示我们变得越来越孤独。 是的，
lonelier yeah which is a word you used
孤独，这个词是你
central to your mission the word
在你的使命中反复提及的核心——
loneliness 52% of Americans report to
孤独。52%的美国人表示
feeling lonely and 57% of Americans
感到孤独，57%的美国人
report to eating their meals alone Etc
表示独自用餐等等。
so something's clearly failing isn't it
所以显然有些地方出了问题，不是吗？
something's clearly not working in this
在
pursuit of connection and social
追求人际关系、社交
connection and social media Etc yeah and
联系以及社交媒体等方面，显然有些地方行不通。是的，
I think so loneliness has been a problem
我认为孤独这个问题已经悄然困扰
that I think has been creeping up on us
我们
for a while but it's really started to
一段时间了，但
accelerate in the last few years and if
在过去几年里，它确实开始加速恶化。如果
you look at you know I've seen charts
你看看图表，比如我见过的那些图表，它们
that show like time spent together in
显示了
real life with friends and time spent
与朋友在现实生活中相处的时间和
consuming media uh consuming like
花在媒体上（比如在
digital media on apps and it's like over
应用程序上）的时间。在
the last like 20 years the one has
过去的20年里，前者
almost completely displaced the other we
几乎完全取代了后者。我们
used to spend hours a day with friends
过去平均每天会花几个小时与朋友
in real life on average um and make like
在现实生活中相处，建立
having genuine connections seeing and
真正的联系，彼此见面和被
being seen and now people are virtually
见面。而现在，人们
almost always consuming some form of
几乎总是在消费某种形式的
digital media or they're working so even
数字媒体，或者忙于工作。所以即使
when you're at the gym you're probably
在健身房，你可能也在
like listening to you know a uh like
听……
whatever like a music or a podcast or
不管是什么，比如听音乐、听播客，或者
you are nothing wrong with that
你听这些都没什么错，
Justin nothing wrong with that listen
贾斯汀，这没什么错。听着，
get rid of M we're not designed to be
摆脱M吧，我们生来就不是为了被
deleted fine because you're because
删除的。没关系，
because you're conscious I mean so and
因为你有意识，我的意思是，
I'm not saying all media consumption is
我不是说所有媒体消费都是
bad I'm saying that like when you are
坏事，我的意思是，当
but when you're pulled in all day and
你整天沉迷其中，
it's completely displaced like you're no
完全被它占据，比如你
longer talking with friends because
不再和朋友说话，而是像
you're just like Doom scrolling on
末日战士一样在
social media platform X Y or Z you've
社交媒体平台X、Y或Z上不停地刷屏，
you've really we've really lost
你真的失去了
something and I think it's that I think
一些东西。我认为，
more than anything has led to this like
这比其他任何因素都更能导致
loneliness I'm so interested in the
孤独感的危机级加速蔓延。我对
disparity between men and women in
男女在约会方面的差异非常感兴趣，这些
over the years on this podcast about
年来，我们在这个播客里就此进行了很多讨论，
this but even in your app you see a big
即使在你的应用里，你也能看到约会应用上排名
disparity between like the bottom 50% of
后50%的
men or the bottom group of men on dating
男性
apps and like the top one or two% of men
和排名前1%或2%的男性之间存在着
completely honest much of the reason why
巨大的差距。坦白说，
I never use dating apps is is I had no
我从不使用约会应用的主要原因之一就是…… 我一直没
success I would get like no good matches
成功，根本匹配不到合适的人。
I was a 18 19 20 year-old kid that had
我当时是个18、19、20岁的毛头小子，一无所有，邋里邋遢，
nothing was super scruffy had no money I
身无分文，
had no chance on these apps and I had
在这些约会软件上根本没戏。我有
this best friend called Logan who looks
个好朋友叫洛根，他看起来就像是从
like he comes out of like a Calvin Klein
卡尔文·克莱恩
ad we were both broke yeah yeah but he
广告里走出来的一样。我们俩都很穷，没错，没错，但他
could go on those apps and he would he
可以用那些软件，而且他会把自己打扮得
would clean up and I look over at him I
漂漂亮亮的。我看着他，
Think Jesus Christ like what's left for
心想：我的天哪，我还有什么机会？说
me I genuinely believe and people might
真的，我觉得
find this quite shocking in my life I've
这很不可思议，但人们可能会觉得我这辈子只约会过
been on five dates in my entire life my
五次。我的
strategy is I go all in so the minute my
策略就是全力以赴。所以，我
current girlfriend said she wanted to go
现在的女朋友一说想
on a date with me I pulled up an Excel
和我约会，我就立刻打开一个Excel
document and it was a three-day like
表格，里面列了一个三天行程的计划。我完全投入进去了。
itinerary I just went all in I've only
我这辈子只约会过
been on five dates in my life but I but
五次，但我很能
I emphasize with men that really
理解那些
struggle with dating apps and have
在约会软件上苦苦挣扎、最终
become disillusioned in fact when we had
感到失望的男人们。事实上，当我们遇到……
I think it was Whitney wolf Herdon from
我记得是Bumble上的惠特尼·沃尔夫·赫登……
Bumble um I was really surprised because
我真的很惊讶，因为
those men showed up in the comment
那些男人都出现在评论
section and they felt like they've been
区里。 他们感觉自己被
forgotten
遗忘了，
about so uh it's a big I mean it's a big
所以这对
Focus for us and we I mean part of this
我们来说是一个很大的关注点。一部分原因
is like larger cultural forces that I
是更大的文化因素在
think are at work but um part of it are
起作用，但另一部分是
things that we can really address I
我们可以在
think within dating apps and some people
约会软件内部解决的问题。有些人很
just good at dating apps and some people
擅长使用约会软件，而有些人虽然很适合约会，
I think are quite datable but they're
但却
just not good at dating apps and it's I
不擅长。我
think the question is like how do we
认为问题在于，我们如何
help really make it a much more focused
帮助他们打造一个更加注重
quality over quantity experience how do
质量而非数量的体验？
we help the people that are struggling
我们如何帮助那些正在苦苦挣扎的人？
this is where I actually think a lot of
我认为
through Ai and generative AI is going to
人工智能和生成式人工智能的潜力就在于此，它们将
like really help us coach people who
真正帮助我们指导那些
aren't finding success and help them
没有找到伴侣的人，帮助他们
find better success and create matches
获得更大的成功，并创造更加
that a much more like quality over
注重质量而非
quantity I mean that when we rebooted h
数量的匹配。我的意思是，当我们重启Hinge时，
you want to make it more quality over
我们希望它更加注重质量而非
quantity and we went from a world where
数量。过去，
people used to like it used to take a
人们需要
thousand swipes in order to get on a
滑动上千次才能
date and in the new hinge it took about
约会，而在新的Hinge中，只需要大约
50 likes so we made a big leap back then
50次点赞。 过去
in terms of helping people get on on
在帮助人们找到理想约会对象方面，这无疑是一次巨大的飞跃。而
dates I think now with AI I think
现在，有了人工智能，我认为
in terms of learning about you learning
在了解你、了解市场上其他用户方面，又迎来了一次全新的飞跃。它能以一种
people up in a in like a really nice
真正友好、
onetoone way and you don't feel like
一对一的方式，帮助你找到合适的伴侣。你不会感觉
you're in this like very owed room where
自己身处一个被完全掌控的房间，
you know some all the attractions you
所有吸引力
know or all the attentions going to just
或关注都集中在
a certain group of people and so I think
特定人群身上。所以
there is a like I think the future is
我认为，未来
getting brighter for us to be able to
我们能够
solve that problem what are the what is
解决这个问题，前景一片光明。
that disparity I read and this might not
我读到过一些关于男女在约会应用上获得关注度差异的文章，虽然可能并不完全
be accurate um a 2021 study by hinch
准确。Hinch 在 2021 年的一项研究
found that the top 1% of men on the app
发现，该应用上排名前 1% 的男性用户
receed more than 16% of all of the likes
获得了超过 16% 的点赞，
while the top 1% of women receive just
而排名前 1% 的女性用户仅获得了
over 11% this indicates a significant
略高于 11% 的点赞。这表明，在约会应用上，
disparity in the level of attention men
男性和女性获得的关注度存在显著差异。Bumble 也存在
similar things from Bumble um a 2022
类似的情况。Bumble 在 2022 年
study by Bumble found that men send an
的一项研究发现，男性
average of 13 messages per day on the
平均每天发送 13 条消息。 在
app while women only send roughly three
约会软件上，女性平均每天只发送三条
messages per day this suggests that men
信息，这表明男性在主动
to initiate conversations on dating apps
发起对话方面投入了更多精力。
and then more broadly from that we've
更广泛地说，我们播
had people on this podcast like Scott
客节目中曾邀请过斯科特·
Galloway that talks about how the very
加洛韦（Scott Galloway）这样的嘉宾，他谈到，最
top 10 10% or the top group of men are
顶尖的10%男性群体
having all the sex and basically there's
占据了所有性生活，而底层男性群体则处于
this kind of like disillusion
一种幻灭和失落的状态，他们
men who are having no sex and are aren't
没有性生活，
finding relationships and aren't having
找不到伴侣，也无法建立
intimate connection and it's that group
亲密关系。加洛韦
of men that he says are the most
认为，这部分男性群体最为
dangerous of all because they're like
危险，因为他们是
lonely broke disillusioned young men we
孤独、贫穷、迷茫的年轻人。我们还有很多工作要做，我们有
major opportunity to help those people
机会帮助那些
that are struggling to find their person
正在苦苦寻找另一半的人，
by helping them zero in better on the
帮助他们更精准地找到
person that they like and and the person
自己喜欢的人，以及可能也
who will like them back helping them put
喜欢自己的人，帮助他们展现
their best foot forward and make sure
自己最好的一面，确保
that they are not shooting eles in the
他们不会
foot by like choosing the wrong photos
因为选择错误的照片、
answered on prompts or any of those
在提问环节只得到一个字的回答等等而弄巧成拙。
types of things so that I think is the
我认为
the key is like so like a big effort at
关键在于…… 所以，
at hinge right now internally we're
目前Hinge内部正在大力推进一项工作，我们
calling it flat in the power curve but
称之为“权力曲线趋于平缓”。
it's it's it's essentially that it's
本质上，它指的是
like how do you help the people who
如何帮助那些
aren't getting to success how do you
尚未获得成功的人，如何
level them up to get to success and then
提升他们的能力，最终走向成功，以及
how do you focus the people so that um
如何引导用户专注于真正感兴趣的对象，从而避免
on in society and on dating apps we
社会和约会软件中普遍存在的权力曲线效应。我们
think we can actually correct what's
认为，通过约会软件，我们可以更有效地纠正
going on more largely in society through
社会中普遍存在的这种现象。具体来说，
apps and so I'm clear we do that by
我们通过
coaching people to be better at dating
指导用户更好地使用约会
apps basically like picking better
软件来实现这一点，例如选择更合适的
pictures understanding better ways to
照片，学习更有效的
reply we do that by helping them match
回复方式。我们帮助他们匹配
with people that are more suitable to
更适合
them and that are more likely to yeah
自己、更有可能发展成恋人的人。
and I think giving like better more warm
我认为，提供更友好、更真诚的
introductions so that people have a
介绍，能够让用户
people have more focus and more of a
更专注，更有发展机会。同时，
chance and you also limit like what's
我们也会限制
going on in terms of um people sending
用户发送过多的点
too many likes or matching too much and
赞或匹配，
getting them to focus on the people that
引导他们专注于
they actually really want so that you
真正想找的人，
don't over engage the rest of the user
避免过度占用其他用户资源。那么，如何引导
people to go from the app to the real
用户从……过渡到……呢？ 把应用应用到现实
world because I was I would always be
世界，因为我一直都很
super scared of that yeah I mean there's
害怕。是的，我的意思是，嗯，这就是
uh that's the whole point of our app and
我们应用的全部意义所在，也是
that's very much what we're like pushing
我们努力引导
people towards um but yeah I mean the
用户走向的方向。但是，是的，我的意思是，
whole the whole funnel is a challenge in
整个流程都是一个挑战，比如如何让
people to sign up getting people to like
人们注册、
create profiles getting people to match
创建个人资料、匹配、
getting people to like move from a match
从匹配
to conversation and conversation to date
到对话、从对话到约会。
you mentioned AI big topic of
你提到了人工智能，
conversation this year of course um
这当然是今年的热门话题，
generative Ai and how that might be able
生成式人工智能以及它如何
to help people find their person I mean
帮助人们找到另一半。我的意思是，关于人工智能、
relationships and dating has always been
人际关系和约会的讨论一直都
quite pessimistic because people are
比较悲观，因为人们会
thinking about sex robots and stuff
想到性爱机器人之类的东西。是的，那
certainly not going to be what Hing is
肯定不是Hing正在研究的，那肯定不是Hing正在研究的。你刚才简要地
mentioned it briefly there but I want to
提到了人工智能，但我想要
make sure I'm
确认一下，
specifically you can give me feedback
你具体如何给我反馈？比如，他们
they've released their I think one level
发布了什么功能？我认为其中一个层面
of it is like just thinking like how do
是思考如何
you make the the dating app experience
改进约会应用的体验。
better how do you help people build
你帮助人们打造
better profiles how do you help coach
更完善的个人资料，那么你如何指导
people through the conversation process
他们完成对话流程，最终促成
and help them move off to a date so you
约会呢？
can certainly like coach people be like
当然，你可以指导他们，比如“
hey you should choose these types of
嘿，你应该选择这类
photos or whatever like all that is
照片”等等，所有这些都是
possible with AI what I think like the
人工智能可以实现的。但我认为
bigger leap though is to move much
更大的飞跃在于更
closer to what feels like a Matchmaker
接近于“媒人”
model and that I think starts to solve
模式，我认为这可以解决
some of the problems that that what you
你刚才提到的一些问题，比如用户
were just talking about where it's less
不再
like you're just sitting there
只是坐在那里
evaluating and that that whole idea of
评估，而是更接近于
like creating a profile
创建个人资料、匹配、
matching trying to chat trying to move
聊天、最终促成约会的模式。就像
it off to a date like when you work with
与
a Matchmaker you just have an interview
媒人合作一样，他们会进行面试，
and they learn Who You Are they go out
了解你是谁，然后去
and interview other people and they say
面试其他人，说“
hey we think you all should meet we'll
嘿，我们觉得你们应该见一面，我们会
set up the date and then after the date
安排约会”，约会结束后
I'm going to follow up to see how it
我会跟进，了解情况
went and provide some feedback
并提供一些反馈。
interesting I think we can get closer
很有意思，我认为我们可以越来越
and closer to that model where we're
接近这种模式，
like going almost straight to setting up
几乎可以直接安排
dates that are with a much higher
约会，而且
likelihood of success than sort of
成功率会比让
leaving it on the user to create a
用户自己创建
personal advertisement for thems and you
个人资料、
know do all the work to sort of find
完成所有事情高得多。 努力寻找
through people that are going to like
那些会喜欢
them that are going to that will like
他们、也会喜欢他们的人。
ET the word Company by definition means
公司一词的定义就是
group of people um you talk about hiring
一群人。你在原则中经常谈到招聘，
generally in this book principle number
这本书的
five here is people with heart hire
第五条原则是：招聘有心人，招聘那些
people who embody the core values I I've
体现核心价值观的人。我从事
business that hiring is really Central
商业的时间越长，就越明白招聘
to everything um culture being the thing
对一切都至关重要。文化是把
that binds those group of people
这些人凝聚
together but what have you learned about
在一起的东西。那么，你从招聘中学到了什么？如果让你对
maybe your younger self that is 20 12
2012年
when you relaunching the new hinge what
重新推出Hinge时的自己说些什么，
would you say to that guy that you know
你会说什么？关于招聘，你现在了解的那个人会说什么？
now about hiring we made a whole lot of
我们一开始犯了很多
hiring mistakes in the beginning and um
招聘错误，但
and it was still we sort of did it like
我们仍然按照
we did the principles which is we looked
原则来做，那就是研究哪些
at okay who are the people who have
人
succeeded at hinge what are their
在Hinge取得了成功，他们有哪些
attributes who are the people who have
特质；哪些人
not succeeded at hinge and like what are
在Hinge没有取得成功，他们又有哪些
their attributes and then we started to
特质。然后我们开始为
just create attributes for like who like
成功者和失败者设定特质，并
started to design an interview which we
开始设计面试流程，我们
call the culture interview which still
称之为…… 文化面试，
everyone goes through it hinge which is
每个人都要经历，它
enally like assesses for those
本质上是对员工特质的评估。这显著
increase in success making sure that we
提高了我们的成功率，确保新
you know when people came they didn't
员工
quit or weren't fired within their first
在第一年内不会离职或被解雇。
year and um now we have extraordinarily
现在，
low attrition at hinge especially
Hinge的员工流失率极低，尤其是
voluntary attrition um and I think it's
自愿离职率。我认为这是
because we focus so much on making sure
因为我们非常注重招聘拥有
we get people in who have those values
这些价值观的人。
and then once you have people in who
一旦员工拥有这些价值观，
have those values and they're all around
并且他们身边都是
other people who have those values that
拥有这些价值观的人，
it's like a place they want to stay
他们就会想要留下来，
because it feels it they feel so aligned
因为他们感觉与同事非常契合。
if there was if you had to get rid of
如果必须舍弃
every value but keep one when it comes
所有价值观，只保留一个，那么在
to hiring a hinge person which one would
招聘Hinge员工时，
you
你会
keep our Three core values are
保留哪个？我们的三大核心价值观是
authenticity and courage and empathy
真实、勇气和同理心。这三者相辅相成，缺一不可，否则就会失去平衡。
like is very imbalanced I think so um
所以，
you want people to be authentic you
我们希望员工真实，但
don't want them to like be so authentic
又不希望他们过于真实、过于
and so blunt that they like are rude and
直率。 他们似乎
mean to people right there's that level
对人粗鲁无礼，这确实体现了
of empathy but I think like those two
同理心的不足。但我认为，
values especially that like authenticity
尤其是真诚——
showing up being who you are saying
展现真实的自我，说出你的想法——才是建立信任的关键。而这种
empathy is ultimately what builds trust
同理心最终能够建立信任，
and I think trust like within an
我认为信任，尤其是在
organization is really the lifeblood of
组织内部，是组织的命脉。
the organization and those two values I
我
think build
认为，真诚和同理心
more trust than anything else they're
比任何其他因素都更能建立信任，它们
like the two ingredients of a great
就像良好关系的两大要素。
relationship 10 years from now we sit
十年后，当我们再次坐在
here and we have another convers ation
这里，
we talk about what hinge is the impact
讨论
it's had on the world what you tell me I
它对世界的影响时，你会告诉我什么？我
think the the next level impact that we
认为，我们
can have in terms of shaping dating
可以在塑造约会
culture and coaching and teaching people
文化、指导和教导人们如何
to become not just better daters but
成为更好的约会者，以及
like we become it's better better people
如何成为更好的人方面，产生更深层次的影响。
really and coaching people how to like
指导人们如何建立
have more harmonious relationships form
更和谐的关系，如何建立
better relationships like I think
更好的人际关系，我认为
there's so much opportunity to guide
有很多机会可以引导
people on that process and and so the
人们完成这个过程。因此，
idea that 10 years from now we like
十年后，如果我们能够
really
真正
shaped dating culture in a way that just
塑造约会文化，让
made everyone more successful that I
每个人都更加成功，我
think is like the vision for where where
认为这就是我们未来的愿景。
headed as you know whoop are a sponsor
正如你所知，Whoop是
of this podcast and I'm an investor in
本播客的赞助商，我也是
the company and last month I had the
这家公司的投资人。上个月，我有
chance to sit down with Kristen Holmes
机会和
she's the VP of performance at whooop
Whoop的绩效副总裁Kristen Holmes坐下来聊了聊。
and I learned so much from our
从我们的对话中，我学到了很多
conversation about circadian rhythms and
关于昼夜节律的知识。
things like sleep studies show that for
睡眠研究表明，
every 45 minutes of sleep debt that you
每多睡45分钟，
acrew that your decision-making ability
你的决策能力
will drop by up to 10% and when you're
就会下降高达10%。如果你
chronically underslept you'll only be a
长期睡眠不足，你只能发挥出自己全部的潜能，无论是作为老板、合作伙伴、朋友还是管理者，你都只能发挥出自己应有的水平。这就是
can be that's why I'm obsessed with
为什么我如此痴迷于
whoop which not just tracks but coaches
Whoop的原因。它不仅能追踪你的睡眠，还能指导
you on how to get better at sleep so you
你如何改善睡眠，让你在
can bring your best to everything that
任何事情上都能发挥出最佳状态。
you choose to do if you're not convinced
如果你还不相信，
you can try whoop for 30 days completely
可以免费试用Whoop 30天，完全
risk-free with zero commitment just by
零风险，无需任何承诺，只需
going to join. whoop.com
访问[此处插入链接]即可加入。  whoop.com 的
CEO that's join. whoop.com
CEO 加入了。  whoop.com 的
CEO and let me know how you get on if
CEO，如果你不喜欢，请告诉我你的感受，
join. whoop.com
加入没有任何义务。  whoop.com 的
CEO we have a closing tradition on this
CEO，我们这个播客有个结尾的传统，上
podcast where the last guest leaves a
一位嘉宾会给下一位嘉宾留下一个
question for the next guest not knowing
问题，而下一位嘉宾并不知道是
who they're going to leave at 4 and the
谁。
question that's been left for you
留给你的问题
is if you could go back in time and give
是：如果你能回到过去，给
advice to your 10-year-old
十岁的
self what would it
自己一条建议，你会说什么？
oh what comes to mind if I could have
哦，我想到的是，如果我能让
impressed on myself that
自己明白，比如，我
are I mean impressed on myself that idea
是说，让我明白
of intrinsic worth if I could have like
内在价值的概念，如果我能让
let myself know that I was worthy no
自己知道，
matter what regardless of like who
无论发生什么，无论谁
dumped me or who ostracized me um that's
抛弃我，无论谁排斥我，我都是有价值的……嗯，在
what I wish in some sense I wish I could
某种程度上，我希望我能
have understood and in the other sense
理解这一点。另一方面，
it's like shaped my entire life and is
这塑造了我的一生，也是
the reason that I have hinge and the
我拥有 Hinge 和
Kate so I think maybe the advice I would
Kate 的原因。所以我想我会给你的建议是：系好
give is just buckle
安全带，
up because it's gonna be a really wild
因为这将是一段非常精彩的
ride and it it uh it um you know does
旅程，而且……你知道，
have a way of working out in the end
最终一切都会好起来的。
thank you so much thank you thank you so
非常感谢，非常感谢，
much pleasure you've built a really
非常荣幸，你创建了一家
incredible company uh you've built a
非常棒的公司。 你打造了一个
different business and that's that's so
与众不同的商业模式，这一点
evident in the product that is hinge in
在你的产品 Hinge 上体现得淋漓尽致。在这个
a market where there's a lot of people
市场里，很多人都在
doing the same obvious thing going for
做着同样的事情，试图
the lwh hanging fruit it was so clear to
摘取唾手可得的果实。
me from a very long distance that at
我隔着很远的距离就能看出，Hinge 的创始人始终遵循
some point someone was being Guided by
着
first principles because you went an an
最初的原则。因为随着
favor as Society has evolved and we've
社会的发展，这条看似显而易见的道路最终对你有利。
people are dissatisfied with not
人们厌倦了肤浅的东西，对
actually the promise of these apps not
这些应用程序未能兑现的承诺感到不满。
being realized which was you told me you
你曾告诉我，你
were going to help me find love yeah and
会帮我找到爱情，但
three or four years later and feeling
三四年过去了，我仍然在使用这个应用程序，滑动屏幕，却感到
despair maybe even feeling worse than I
绝望，甚至比刚开始使用时更糟。Hinge
different route and when you describe
另辟蹊径。当你向
hinge to someone you say it's an app
别人介绍 Hinge 时，你会说它
that cares more about meaning that cares
更注重意义，
more about fostering deep connections
更注重培养深层次的联系。
and that as you say in your own words
正如你自己所说，它会
slows things down a little bit so you
放慢节奏，让你有
can take the time to find a much more um
时间去寻找一段比其他约会软件更
real
真实、更有潜力、更
authentic potentially successful Bond
成功的缘分。
that's why hinge has always been I think
这就是 Hinge 成功的原因。 我一直认为它
has always represented the future
代表着未来，
because at the end of the day people are
因为归根结底，人们使用
coming on these apps to find love and
这些应用程序是为了寻找爱情。
it's clear to me this whole design to be
对我来说，整个“设计即
deleted thing that and from everybody
删除”的理念非常明确，而且
that I've met at hinge that that is a
我从在Hinge遇到的每个人那里都了解到，这是
promise you are genuinely trying to
你们真心实意想要
deliver upon yeah I mean it's totally
兑现的承诺。是的，这完全
true and that idea of first principles
正确，从第一性原理出发的想法也完全
is exactly right I think you have to
正确。我认为你必须从头开始
just like rethink from the ground up
重新思考，
like how would I build this and stop
比如“我该如何构建它”，而不是想着“哦，
thinking like oh other apps do this
其他应用程序这样做，
we'll do this with this twist and that I
我们也要这样做，并加以改进”。我
think is what
认为，这正是
initially you don't find success during
你最初在这个过程中无法取得成功的原因，
that path because everyone's like well
因为每个人都会说“
this is different this is weird there's
这不一样，这很奇怪，
no blueprint right and um but over time
没有蓝图可循”。但是随着时间的推移，
comes from actually building an
真正打造一款
effective product that grows through
有效的、通过口碑传播的产品所带来的复利效应会让
word of mouth is is you just and now
你受益匪浅。
today Hing is you know the fastest
如今，Hinge是英国和澳大利亚
growing major dating app or the number
增长最快的主流约会应用程序，排名
one app in the UK and Australia and and
第一，并且正在
um quickly growing in in Europe to
迅速发展成为
become like a top dating app in Europe
欧洲顶级约会应用程序之一。
so it's it pays off eventually you have
所以，最终会有回报的。你必须
to be very patient I see that in great
非常有耐心，我看到了这一点。
Founders you know I see saw it in the
你知道，我从Wop的创始人身上看到了这一点，
that they made because they're so Guided
他们做出了一些看似不合常理的决定，因为他们深受
by their first principles usually based
第一原则的指引，而这些原则通常
on the Founder's personal experience and
基于创始人的个人经历。
that's what I see in hinge so thank you
我在Hinge身上也看到了这一点。所以，感谢你
for creating an app that I consider to
创造了一款我认为
be a really great one and a really
非常出色且
important one and being someone who's
意义非凡的应用程序，感谢你致力于
driven to end loneliness ultimately um
最终消除孤独，
and bring people together because it's
并将人们聚集在一起，因为这在
never been more important than it is now
今天比以往任何时候都更加重要。
thank you Justus thank
谢谢你，Justus。谢谢。接下来，我想
you quick one from one of our sponsors a
快速回答一位赞助商的问题。
about hu over the years about where he
多年来，很多人问过我关于Hinge的问题，比如它
fits into your life is it the most
在生活中扮演着怎样的角色，以及在考虑营养时，它是否是最
healthy choice one can make when they're
健康的选择。
here's what I would say to all of those
我想对所有这样的
people I think in an Ideal World I would
人说的是，在理想情况下，我当然希望能够
be able to sit down and cook and prepare
坐下来自己烹饪和准备
all of my meals I think that would be my
所有餐食，这对我来说才是
ideal option but it because of the
最理想的选择。但由于
nature of my life because I'm moving
我的生活方式，我经常四处奔波，所以在使用Hinge
around often what used to happen before
之前，
hu was I'd end up making bad choices I'd
我常常会做出不健康的选择，比如吃
end up snacking I'd have junk food
零食，选择垃圾食品。
options on the go because I was busy and
因为我工作繁忙，
my nutrition would come second to
营养往往被工作放在次要位置。hu 让我随时随地都能
what hu allows you to do is to have a
享用更
healthier option on the go that is
健康的饮品，方便快捷，
convenient that contains a lot of the
富含多种
nutrients that you need to have a
营养成分，满足你
complete diet and that's exactly where
均衡的饮食需求。它完美契合
it fits in my life they've now expanded
我的生活。现在 hu 的产品
the range if you haven't yet checked out
线已经扩展，如果你还没体验过
the hu RTD I highly recommend you do go
hu 即饮饮品，我强烈推荐你去
to your local Tesco boots or Saints
附近的 Tesco、Boots 或 Saints
spres or onine online and you can grab
Spres 门店，或者在线购买试用。接下来，
there do you need a podcast to listen to
你需要一个播客节目来听吗？
next we've discovered that people who
我们发现，
liked this episode also tend to
喜欢这期节目的听众往往也很
absolutely love another recent episode
喜欢
we've done so I've linked that episode
我们最近推出的另一期节目，所以我把那期节目的链接放在
in the description below I know you'll
下面的简介里了，相信你会
enjoy
喜欢。
[Music]
[音乐]